<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Charlie Puth</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Charlie Puth</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 14:38:05 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - We Don't Talk Anymore [DROELOE Remix] - Key of Am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-we-don-t-talk-anymore-droeloe-remix/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: F G Am

We Don’t Talk Anymore by Charlie Puth, featuring Selena Gomez.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones to beginner ukulele students can play along.

Link to Original: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3AtDnEC4zak

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-we-don-t-talk-anymore-droeloe-remix/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - Attention - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-attention/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Attention on the ukulele by Charlie Puth. The chords used are Em D Bm C.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-attention/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - Done for Me - Key of Bm]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-done-for-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Done For Me by Charlie Puth featuring Kehlani on the ukulele. The chords used are Bm7 Abdim7 Gmaj7 C#m7 F#7.

*The Abdim7 should be G#dim7 but I couldn't find the diagram in the chord font I use. Had to use the enharmonic.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-done-for-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - Done for Me - Key of Am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-done-for-me-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Done For Me by Charlie Puth featuring Kehlani on the ukulele. The chords used are Am7 F#dim7 F Bm7 E7.

*Made this version to make it a little easier for my students to play. If you want the original version in the original key click here https://youtu.be/o_xHOa4DsoQ

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-done-for-me-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - One Call Away - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-one-call-away/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  The original is in C#, so this is lowered a half step from the original.

As performed by Charlie Puth.

There is an existing ukulele play along video (https://youtu.be/SlqINOuqGtc) by Dr. A, one of the original creators of this style of play along video, but I wanted to add color string fretboard charts and Color Chord as well.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS and DR Multi-Color ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-one-call-away/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - One Call Away - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-one-call-away-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[FOR UKULELE:
"One Call Away" as performed by Charlie Puth.
Key of C with chords and lyrics.
Chords: C, F, G, Am]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charlie-puth-one-call-away-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>