<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » Cadd9</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Chord » Cadd9</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:38:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ziv Zaifman - A Million Dreams - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ziv-zaifman-a-million-dreams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As heard in The Greatest Showman.

Also visit the version by Kris Gilbert: https://youtu.be/0_auBl2YMEQ

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ziv-zaifman-a-million-dreams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Guns N' Roses - Sweet Child O' Mine - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/guns-n-roses-sweet-child-o-mine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[D, A, G, C, C-add9, Em...and a little bit of picking.  Strum pattern is in there along with a bit of a picking practice (80% speed, 90%, 100%.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/guns-n-roses-sweet-child-o-mine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Grace VanderWaal - Moonlight - Key of Em]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/grace-vanderwaal-moonlight/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Em.

As performed by Grace VanderWaal

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/grace-vanderwaal-moonlight/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Extreme - More Than Words - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/extreme-more-than-words/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Extreme.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/extreme-more-than-words/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Try Ukulele Play Along - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/try-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use: A ukulele play along based on Mandy Harvey's performance on "America's Got Talent" (audio from that video).  In the Key of D: G, D, Am, Cadd9, CMaj7.  (I forgot to list D on the title screen).  Note the use of Cadd9 and some suggested "other" fingerings for other chords (e.g. D) which may make it easier to switch between chords.

Mandy Harvey is a singer/songwriter who lost her hearing at age 18 while pursuing a degree in music education; she now writes songs and sends recordings away to have them be transcribed, and she also learns music by watching a tuner on her iPhone.

By all means, support Mandy Harvey...purchase her recordings, watch AGT and the AGT videos on YouTube, watch the various interviews with Mandy Harvey, etc.

The ukulele font is Chordette for Education from ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/try-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phillip Phillips - Gone, Gone, Gone - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/phillip-phillips-gone-gone-gone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulule Play-Along
I raised the pitch of the song up a half-step.
The chord names sound very complicated but they aren't. Check out the beginning of the video to see how they are so closely related. It's really interesting!
Strumming and picking suggestions provided.

I do not own the copyright to this music. Video is for educational and instructional purposes]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/phillip-phillips-gone-gone-gone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Counting Crows - Big Yellow Taxi - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/counting-crows-big-yellow-taxi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chords used:  D, G,  Cadd9  (very easy--only 2 fingers needed to play this chord)
I've lowered the pitch of the song by one half-step to fit the ukelele a bit better.

I do not own the copyright to this music.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/counting-crows-big-yellow-taxi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>