<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Luis Fonsi</title>
    <link>http://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Luis Fonsi</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 02:15:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luis Fonsi - Llegaste Tú]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi-llegaste-tú/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Llegaste Tu on the ukulele by Luis Fonsi and Juan Luis Guerra. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Em F#dim.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi-llegaste-tú/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luis Fonsi, Daddy Yankee - Despacito]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi,-daddy-yankee-despacito/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi,-daddy-yankee-despacito/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luis Fonsi, Demi Lovato - Échame la Culpa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi,-demi-lovato-échame-la-culpa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Échame La Culpa by Luis Fonsi and Demi Lovato on the ukulele. The chords used are C F G Am.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi,-demi-lovato-échame-la-culpa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luis Fonsi, Daddy Yankee - Despacito (Remix) ft. Justin Bieber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi,-daddy-yankee-despacito-ft.-justin-bieber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Here's an ukulele play-along video made for beginning ukulele players in an easy key. I do not own the copyright to this song and it is intended for educational purposes only. Enjoy!

This is the fixed version - my first attempt I messed up the timing on the changes.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/luis-fonsi,-daddy-yankee-despacito-ft.-justin-bieber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>