<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » B7</title>
    <link>http://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Chord » B7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:23:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beyoncé - SPIRIT (From Disney's "The Lion King")]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/beyoncé-spirit/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Chords Used: G D Em C B7 Am F

Spirit (from Disney’s The Lion King) by Beyoncé.  It’s been raised by 2 semitones and the modulation has been removed so beginner ukulele students can play along.  Also, the “quick change” chords have not been included.  As for the B7 chord, feel free to do it 432X instead of using the barre.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/beyoncé-spirit/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim McGraw - Live Like You Were Dying]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/tim-mcgraw-live-like-you-were-dying/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: The first two verses are in the key of G and uses G, C, Em, D, and 1 B7.  The third verse is in the key of A and uses A, D, Gbm, E, and 1 C#.

Live Like You Were Dying by Tim McGraw.  It’s the official lyric video, I just added the ukulele chords.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/tim-mcgraw-live-like-you-were-dying/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Duplessis - Lemonade - Alex Boye]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/jerry-duplessis-lemonade---alex-boye/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Lemonade on the ukulele by Alex Boye. The chords used are G C D B7 Cm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/jerry-duplessis-lemonade---alex-boye/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick and Justin Timberlake - True Colors]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-and-justin-timberlake-true-colors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play True Colors on the ukulele by Anna Kendrick and Justin Timberlake. The chords used are G C D Em B7. Original in Key E.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-and-justin-timberlake-true-colors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amos Lee - Sweet Pea]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/amos-lee-sweet-pea/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Simplified the chords slightly and took out the Barre chord.

This tutorial will show you how to play Sweet Pea on the ukulele by Amos Lee. The chords used are G D7 B7 A7 Em7 Am7. Original in E.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/amos-lee-sweet-pea/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paramore - Interlude: Moving On]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/paramore-interlude:-moving-on/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Updated version.

As performed by Paramore.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/paramore-interlude:-moving-on/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Perry Como - It's Beginning to Look a Lot Like Christmas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/perry-como-it's-beginning-to-look-a-lot-like-christmas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along - Its Beginning To Look Like Xmas

It's Beginning To Look Like Christmas - Perry Como
Written by Meredith Willson

Using the chords: A  A7  Am  B7  C  D  D7  E7  Em  G  G7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU

The audio has been adjusted to suit the ukulele better



This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/perry-como-it's-beginning-to-look-a-lot-like-christmas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter, Paul and Mary - Light One Candle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/peter,-paul-and-mary-light-one-candle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Peter, Paul, and Mary.

This tune is a favorite song of the Twin Cities Ukulele Club.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/peter,-paul-and-mary-light-one-candle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Aldo Milani - Chicca]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/aldo-milani-chicca/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along - Walking In A Winter Wonderland

Winter Wonderland - Dean Martin
Written by Felix Bernard (music) and Richard B. Smith (lyricist)


Using the chords: A7  B7  C  Dm  D7  E7  G  G7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU



This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/aldo-milani-chicca/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Von Trapp Children - Hot Cup Of Cocoa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/the-von-trapp-children-hot-cup-of-cocoa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of D.  Lowered from the original and kept in one key (The original is in Eb and E).  In the intro area, I did not add the suspensions on the D and A7--feel free to add them as you play (if you wish).

As performed by the Von Trapp Children.

This was a request from Marsha Burton Joss on the Facebook Ukulele Video Play Along Group.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/the-von-trapp-children-hot-cup-of-cocoa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>