<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Creedence Clearwater Revival</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Creedence Clearwater Revival</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:20:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Creedence Clearwater Revival - Up Around The Bend]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/creedence-clearwater-revival-up-around-the-bend/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/creedence-clearwater-revival-up-around-the-bend/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Creedence Clearwater Revival - Down On The Corner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/creedence-clearwater-revival-down-on-the-corner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Creedence Clearwater Revival.

This play along was originally created by Dr. A (https://youtu.be/dW5Zrtt634E) but I wanted a version that showed the next chord...and I also added KIDS colored strings and Color Chord play along boxes.  I would never ask someone to re-create their work for my preferences, so I recreated the video.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/creedence-clearwater-revival-down-on-the-corner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Creedence Clearwater Revival - Bad Moon Rising]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/creedence-clearwater-revival-bad-moon-rising/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Just G, D, and A!

Check out the website for the ukulele jam sessions I run via Fredonia Ukulele: https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.edu/fredonia-ukulele/

Check out my website for music teachers:
https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.edu/reese-ukulele/]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/creedence-clearwater-revival-bad-moon-rising/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>