<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » Asus4</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Chord » Asus4</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 15:35:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Bad Liar - Baritone Ukulele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/imagine-dragons-bad-liar-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.

Chords Used: D, Bm, G, A, F#, Asus4

Key of D, lowered a half step from the original in Eb.

As performed by Imagine Dragons.

Tutorial Video (GCEA): Go to https://youtu.be/cTdAiw4Ox-M

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is based on Chordette for Education (Chordette is available from ukefarm.com, but the baritone font I am using is not yet available from ukefarm).

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/imagine-dragons-bad-liar-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Josh Groban - Believe - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/josh-groban-believe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of D.  Lowered from the original key of E.

As performed by Josh Groban.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/josh-groban-believe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Moby - Sunday - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/moby-sunday/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Words & music by Moby & Sylvia Robinson.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/moby-sunday/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thompson Twins - Hold Me Now - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/thompson-twins-hold-me-now/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chords: D, Bm7, C, A, Asus4, B-flat6  Strum pattern...D, D, D, DU, DU, DU, DU, DU.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/thompson-twins-hold-me-now/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash - Love's Been Good To Me - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-love-s-been-good-to-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Here's one for those who fancy a little challenge. Tip: play only every second chord. The good thing is, once you master this track you have improved a lot in your uke playing!

Performed by Johnny Cash
Written by Rod McKuen

This video is created for an educational purpose. All rights belong to their respectful owners.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-love-s-been-good-to-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oasis - Wonderwall - Key of Em]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/oasis-wonderwall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Em, G, C, D, Dsus4, A7, A7sus4.  Syncopated strum pattern. See the Wonderwall Strum Guide Video (https://youtu.be/4dqoZWCVoVM).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/oasis-wonderwall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>