<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Avicii</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Avicii</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:20:04 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Avicii - Waiting For Love]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avicii-waiting-for-love/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use  Chords: Am, Em, F, G, & Dm]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avicii-waiting-for-love/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Avicii - Wake Me Up]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avicii-wake-me-up/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Lowered a whole step from the original recording.

As performed by Avicii.

Based on a ukulele play along by Dr. Reese (https://youtu.be/7tNG1J2ybgo).  I wanted to use our color ukulele chord diagrams, and added the color “boxes” that correspond with Kala’s new Color Chord Ukulele.  I also wanted to see where we were going to stop ahead of time.  I slowed the song down a touch (96% of the original) and removed some of the repeated break sections.  See Dr. Reese’s video for strumming suggestions...I suggest starting students simply strumming on the beat.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS and DR Multi-Color ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avicii-wake-me-up/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>