<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » R. City</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » R. City</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 15:00:24 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[R. City - Locked Away - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/r-city-locked-away/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Originally in C#, so this version is lowered a half step from the original.

As performed by R City ft. Adam Levine

There is an existing ukulele play along of this song by Dr. Jill Reese, the creator of this genre of play along video (see https://youtu.be/G5k0IexJUDY).   I am making this version for my use, but am sharing it as well.  Please support Dr. Reese and her efforts, as well as the efforts by all of the educators who are creating these videos for classroom and community jam sessions.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS and DR Multi-Color ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/r-city-locked-away/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[R. City - Locked Away - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/r-city-locked-away-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Only C, Am, F, G

Check out the website for the ukulele jam sessions I run via Fredonia Ukulele: https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.e...

Check out my website for music teachers:
https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.e...]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/r-city-locked-away-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>