<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » R&B</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Genre » R&B</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 17:37:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Queen Naija - Butterflies - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/queen-naija-butterflies/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Butterflies on the ukulele by The Queen Naija. The chords used are Gmaj7 Dmaj7 Em7 F#m.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/queen-naija-butterflies/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Withers - Lovely Day - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Lovely Day on the ukulele by Bill Withers. The chords used are F Dm7 Bbmaj7 Bbm7 Cm7 Eb C#maj7(Dbmaj7)

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fats Domino - Blueberry Hill - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/fats-domino-blueberry-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C

As performed by Fats Domino.  I have wanted to do this since hearing about his death on October 24, 2017 (Today is 11/03/2017).  Some of the chords are ambiguous, but the chords as presented work OK.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/fats-domino-blueberry-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Withers - Ain't No Sunshine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bill-withers-ain-t-no-sunshine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Hey! Check my awesome stuff for merch at
https://www.redbubble.com/people/Ukeledu/shop

-

¡Hey! Échale un ojo a mis molones artículos de merchan en
https://www.redbubble.com/es/people/Ukeledu/shop

________________________

STRUMMING PATTERN / RASGUEO:


Main Riff / Riff principal: D   D DUD DUD DUD  D   D  DU   D  DU
'' last part of the Riff / Última parte del Riff: D   D D DU D DU (x2)
Knowledge part / Parte de "I know":  xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx...

D: Down / Hacia abajo
U: Up / Hacia arriba
x: Muted strigs (Down) / Cuerdas muteadas con la palma de la mano (hacia abajo)

________________________

Hey! If you liked this video, give me a like, subscribe and comment your doubts, suggestions or anything you want.

-
¡Hey! Si te ha gustado el vídeo, dame like, suscríbete y comenta tus dudas, sugerencias o lo que te apetezca.

_________________________

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/ukeledu/
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/ukeledu.music/]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bill-withers-ain-t-no-sunshine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash - Folsom Prison Blues - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-folsom-prison-blues/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Folsom Prison Blues by Johnny Cash.  Key of G (G, G7, C, Hawaiian D7).  Note: This is in a higher key than the original song (see the version for the Key of F if interested in singing at the original pitch).  I apologize that this makes Johnny's voice sound a little funny, but these chords approximate the written version in Jim Beloff's "The Daily Ukulele" or "The Yellow Book."

Whenever I attend a ukulele jam, this song is requested.   I am attempting to make play alongs for songs that are fun to play, and for those that are commonly requested at ukulele jams, so that young/new players can feel at home in those jam sessions, being familiar with the "genre" of "popular" ukulele songs.

All rights remain with the music company who holds Johnny Cash's work; any advertisements that appear are for that company--not for this channel.

The ukulele font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com

Created using Keynote (layout, text, & lyrics) Keepvid.com (saving the original YouTube video), Audacity (ripping audio and modifying audio), Preview (working with the transparent "bouncing ball train"), and iMovie (placing the "bouncing ball train" and other edits.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-folsom-prison-blues/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash - Folsom Prison Blues - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-folsom-prison-blues-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Folsom Prison Blues by Johnny Cash.  Key of F (F, F7, Bb, C7).

Whenever I attend a ukulele jam, this song is requested.  This is the original key (lowered slightly in pitch to match A=440)...I will be making a version in a higher key to match the chords in Jim Beloff's The Daily Ukulele.  I am attempting to make play alongs for songs that are fun to play, and for those that are commonly requested at ukulele jams, so that young/new players can feel at home in those jam sessions, being familiar with the "genre" of "popular" ukulele songs.

All rights remain with the music company who holds Johnny Cash's work; any advertisements that appear are for that company--not for this channel.

The ukulele font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com

Created using Keynote (layout, text, & lyrics) Keepvid.com (saving the original YouTube video), Audacity (ripping audio and modifying audio), Preview (working with the transparent "bouncing ball train"), and iMovie (placing the "bouncing ball train" and other edits.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-folsom-prison-blues-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>