<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » P!Nk</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » P!Nk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:08:19 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[P!nk - Just Give Me a Reason - Baritone Ukulele - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-just-give-me-a-reason-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of G. (Original Key)

As performed by Pink, ft. Nate Ruess.

This song was a request from a comment on the Ukulele Tenor YouTube channel.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is based on Chordette for Education (ukefarm.com).  As there isn't a Baritone Ukulele Education font (yet) I tried making my own in Calligraphr.com.  I still have some spacing to work out, it seems.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-just-give-me-a-reason-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[P!nk - Just Give Me a Reason - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-just-give-me-a-reason/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Created with letter names so any non-transposing instrument can play along.  Key of  Key of G. (Original Key)

As performed by Pink, ft. Nate Ruess.

This song was a request from a comment on the Ukulele Tenor YouTube channel.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-just-give-me-a-reason/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[P!nk - What About Us - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-what-about-us/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play What About Us on the ukulele by Pink. The chords used are Em C G.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-what-about-us/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[P!nk - Just Like Fire - Key of Em]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-just-like-fire/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This video is for educational purposes only.  I do not own the rights to the song.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/p-nk-just-like-fire/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>