<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Lucinda Williams</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Lucinda Williams</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:24:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lucinda Williams - Jug Band Music - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lucinda-williams-jug-band-music/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Modified up a quarter note (50 cents) to match A440 pitch.

As performed by Lucinda Williams.

My wife and I had the chance to travel to Memphis, Tennessee this past week (July 2018) on a short vacation with the side goal of joining the Memphis Ukulele Flash Mob at their weekly meeting at Central BBQ, led by Pete McCarty.  It was wonderful all the way around...friendly people, great food, and fun music making.  Pete picked a number of Memphis-related music because we were there, including this song, Jug Band Music (Seems So Sweet).  I didn’t know the song, so I share this version by Lucinda Williams with you, as MUFM shared it with my wife and I.  Are you in Memphis or passing through on a Tuesday night?  I urge you to stop on by...but get there early to order food and to get a chair!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lucinda-williams-jug-band-music/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lucinda Williams - Jug Band Music - Baritone Ukulele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lucinda-williams-jug-band-music-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of C.  Modified up a quarter note (50 cents) to match A440 pitch.

As performed by Lucinda Williams.

My wife and I had the chance to travel to Memphis, Tennessee this past week (July 2018) on a short vacation with the side goal of joining the Memphis Ukulele Flash Mob at their weekly meeting at Central BBQ, led by Pete McCarty.  It was wonderful all the way around...friendly people, great food, and fun music making.  Pete picked a number of Memphis-related music because we were there, including this song, Jug Band Music (Seems So Sweet).  I didn’t know the song, so I share this version by Lucinda Williams with you, as MUFM shared it with my wife and I.  Are you in Memphis or passing through on a Tuesday night?  I urge you to stop on by...but get there early to order food and to get a chair!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lucinda-williams-jug-band-music-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>