<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » Fm</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Fm</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 23:44:06 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Taron Egerton - I'm Still Standing]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/taron-egerton-i-m-still-standing/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Cm and C.  Raised a whole step from the original (Bbm and Bb).  This is an updated video, just for the intro slide and the description.  Sadly, you cannot update a video with a new version on YouTube.  I left a link to this video on the original video.

As performed by Taron Egerton in “Sing.”  I had originally had Taron Egerton's name wrong, and a number of people wrote comments to complain about it.

My boys enjoyed Sing and frequently sing this song.  I had started working on but moved on to other videos.  Katie Denure (One Music School) posted a tutorial today (https://youtu.be/m_Xoe9g00oc), which inspired me to wrap up this video.  I took away some of the fast Ab Bb C changes that occur at the end of some phrases...feel free to add them back in your own practice.  This video offers some good Barre chord practice (partial and full) with Cm, Ab, and Bb.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Visit the sister ukulele channel to this channel, YouTube.com/ukestuff]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/taron-egerton-i-m-still-standing/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[McFly - All About You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mcfly-all-about-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[All About You by McFly.  It’s been digitally lowered by 1 semitone so beginner ukulele students can play along.  For educational use.  Chords Used: C Am F G E7 C7 D7 Fm G+

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mcfly-all-about-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mama Cass - Dream A Little Dream Of Me]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mama-cass-dream-a-little-dream-of-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Dream A Little Dream Of Me - The Mamas & The Paps
Music by Fabian Andre and Wilbur Schwandt and lyrics by Gus Kahn

Using the chords: A  A7  Bm  B7  C  E7  F  Fm  F#m  G7  Ab

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU or DU DU DU DU

This is not an easy play along but with lots of practice it is very playable and devinitely worth the work.


This video is meant for educational purposes and ukulele lessons.

No copyright infringement intended.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mama-cass-dream-a-little-dream-of-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toon Tunes - The Flintstones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/toon-tunes-the-flintstones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C (Transposed down from the original).

Chords Used: G, C, Dm7, D7, G7, Dm, Em, F, E7, A7, Am7, Fm

The theme song from The Flintstones.

Tutorial Video (GCEA & DGBE): https://youtu.be/SxhKRWp3zx0

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is available at ukefarm.com.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6

We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!

Interested in UkeStuff merchandise?  https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And you are invited to visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/toon-tunes-the-flintstones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mickey Mouse Ku’u Lei Melody Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mickey-mouse-kuu-lei-melody-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Transposed down a major third from the original.  Suggestion: if you want to play along with the original song, consider using a capo at the 4th fret and using these chords.

Chords Used: C, Dm, G7, C7, F, Fm, A7, D7, E7

As heard in the Disney Short "Mickey Mouse Ku'u Lei Melody"

https://youtu.be/QDhdMF0qZI8

The song (PDF) was shared on social media by the composer (Christopher Willis) under the name "Pua Nani Ē."

Tutorial Video (GCEA & DGBE): https://youtu.be/A1OW_b1t3u0

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is available at ukefarm.com.

Interested in UkeStuff merchandise?  https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mickey-mouse-kuu-lei-melody-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billie Eilish - party favor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/billie-eilish-party-favor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for CGEA ukulele.  Key of C.

Chords Used: C, Am, F, G, E7, Fm

As performed by Billie Eilish

Tutorial Video (GCEA & DGBE): https://youtu.be/v-Nj_ISkiqk

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font available at ukefarm.com.   The motion background is from https://youtu.be/EWKO4JYYMKU

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/billie-eilish-party-favor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Heartstrings (ukulele play-along)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/heartstrings-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Heartstrings on the ukulele by Kolohe Kai. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Fm E7 Cmaj7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/heartstrings-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Ain't Misbehavin']]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/hank-williams-ain-t-misbehavin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Ain’t Misbehavin’ on the ukulele by Hank Williams Jr. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Em Fm A7 C7 D7 E7 G7 .

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/hank-williams-ain-t-misbehavin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oasis - Don't Look Back in Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/oasis-don-t-look-back-in-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Don't Look Back In Anger - Oasis

Using the chords: Am  C  E7  F  Fm  G

Suggested Strum Patterns: D  D DU    D  D DU  (for fast chords use D DU)


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/oasis-don-t-look-back-in-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Harris - The Bare Necessities]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/phil-harris-the-bare-necessities/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Original Key.

From the Jungle Book.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/phil-harris-the-bare-necessities/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>