<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » F9</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » F9</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 15:51:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Riptide Ukulele Play Along (Large Noises Recording) - Key of Am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/riptide-ukulele-play-along-large-noises-recording/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Am.

As performed by Vance Joy in the video by Large Noises (https://youtu.be/ES_aFUIvBz0).

I have a couple of other videos of this song, and other ukulele play alongs exist as well.  I came across this version tonight, and I think it is my favorite that I have seen in context of trying to play along.  It is Vance in a performance setting (unlike the other video I made where he is on a trolley) with steady volume throughout as well as more consistent tempos than the “official” recording.

Vance plays a baritone ukulele, by the way.

Strumming patterns:

Verses: DD UDU
Chorus: DUX U UXU (X=chuck or chunk)
Bridge: Syncopated rhythm without any repetition.  Lots of heavy strumming!

Finger picking guide appears in the video (H=hammer on)

Can’t play the patterns?  Just have fun and play along.  You can also play DD UDU throughout the whole song if you like.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/riptide-ukulele-play-along-large-noises-recording/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[You Are My Sunshine Uke Play Along for YOUNG CHILDREN - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/you-are-my-sunshine-uke-play-along-for-young-children/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[In this version, students are divided into two groups: one group plays the C chord and the other plays the modified F chord. The teacher plays the verse and any G chord.
Chorus-Verse-Chorus]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/you-are-my-sunshine-uke-play-along-for-young-children/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>