<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Ariana Grande</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Ariana Grande</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 15:00:24 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ariana Grande - Santa Tell Me - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ariana-grande-santa-tell-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along - Christmas

Santa Tell Me - Ariana Grande
Written by Ariana Grande, Ilya Salmanzadeh and Savan Kotecha

Using the chords: A B7 Bm C D Em G G7 Gmaj7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU

Website: http://ukulele.wales/
Ukulele Wales Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQxNRbyi3i4Nvqpo55bWBkg
T-Shirts & Merch: https:https://www.redbubble.com/people/ukulaliens/shop

This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ariana-grande-santa-tell-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ariana Grande - They Don't Know - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ariana-grande-they-don-t-know/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play They Don’t Know on the ukulele by Ariana Grande. The chords used are G C D Em Bm.

*Note - In the progression G G C D if you are playing w a band second G should be G/B, where the bass plays the B or keys plays G on right hand and B on the left hand.
Also, There is a B/D# before each chorus but I left it out to make it easier for beginners.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ariana-grande-they-don-t-know/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ariana Grande - no tears left to cry - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ariana-grande-no-tears-left-to-cry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.

As performed by Ariana Grande.

I saw the Jimmy Fallon/Tonight Show version of this using the Nintendo Switch Labo instruments, and decided to make a ukulele version (using Ariana Grande’s original version of the song).

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/ariana-grande-no-tears-left-to-cry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>