<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Religious</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Religious</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:03:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[He's Got The Whole World In His Hands - Ukulele Play Along Video - Very Easy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/he-s-got-the-whole-world-in-his-hands-ukulele-play-along-video-very-easy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele Play Along - Very Easy

He's Got The Whole World In His Hands - Nursery Rhyme

Using the chords: C and G7

Suggested Strum Pattern - D D D D

Ideal for younger children in primary or elementary school.
This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/he-s-got-the-whole-world-in-his-hands-ukulele-play-along-video-very-easy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lift Every Voice And Sing - Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/lift-every-voice-and-sing-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Lift Every Voice and Sing by the Abyssinian Baptist Church.  It’s been lowered by 3 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.  For educational use.  Chords Used: C, F, A7, Dm, Bbdim, Dm, Gm, A, Bb, D, D7

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/lift-every-voice-and-sing-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Thanksgiving Song - Ukulele Play Along (no lyrics)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-thanksgiving-song-ukulele-play-along-no-lyrics/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[**The same play along song, but with lyrics, may be found here - https://youtu.be/ch5pyySDpEs .

Now Thank We All Our God (Nun Danket), also known as the Thanksgiving Hymn or the Hymn of Thanksgiving.  For educational use.  Chords Used: C F Dm G G7 Am Em A

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-thanksgiving-song-ukulele-play-along-no-lyrics/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Easter Egg Hunt by KizCastle -  Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/easter-egg-hunt-by-kizcastle-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

The pitch has been lowered to make it playable by young ukulele students.

Source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rov5t-aggeQ

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/easter-egg-hunt-by-kizcastle-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Angels We Have Heard on High (Wilson) Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/angels-we-have-heard-on-high-wilson-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G. There is a key change in the original; I have modified the file to remain in G.

As performed by Josh Wilson.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/angels-we-have-heard-on-high-wilson-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[When the Saints Go Marching In]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/when-the-saints-go-marching-in/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Kids-Songs.TV.  It is nearly impossible to find a version of this song in C that uses only 3 chords and stays in C!  This is a transposed (from D) and shortened version of the original video.

Original video:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=giiK_lYsR0Q

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com. The colored font matches Aquila KIDS ukulele strings.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/when-the-saints-go-marching-in/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Laurie London - He's Got the Whole World in His Hands]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/laurie-london-he-s-got-the-whole-world-in-his-hands/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Laurie London

Original video:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cqb3NSiSwoc

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com. The colored font matches Aquila KIDS ukulele strings.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/laurie-london-he-s-got-the-whole-world-in-his-hands/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>