<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » B</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » B</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:49:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Naomi Scott - Speechless ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/naomi-scott-speechless/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for CGEA ukulele.  Key of Em.

Chords Used: Em, D7, C, D, G, Bsus4, B, Am, Bm7

Original performance by Naomi Scott, from the (2019) motion picture "Aladdin"

Earlier today, I had posted a version of this without the "follow the chord boxes."  I'm not quite sure where they went, as I start with the ukulele version and then move to other versions.  So, I have re-uploaded the video.  Sorry for any inconvenience.

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature only video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (GCEA chords & Strumming/Finger Picking): https://youtu.be/aH4_OQ2pNiI

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/naomi-scott-speechless/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Bublé - Someday ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-bublé-someday/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Someday on the ukulele by Michael Bublé and Meghan Trainor. The chords used are G C D Am Em7 plus an optional Uke 2 part that uses A B Cm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-bublé-someday/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dire Straits - Sultans of Swing]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dire-straits-sultans-of-swing/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chords:
Dm, C, F, B-flat, A
Strum pattern - Included in the video
Go to this video to practice the Riff with Quick Changes!!!: https://youtu.be/DfZEcfxpsW0]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dire-straits-sultans-of-swing/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Doobie Brothers - Listen to the Music ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-doobie-brothers-listen-to-the-music/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chords: F, B-flat, Dm, G, C, E-flat
Possible Strum Patterns:
#1 =  Two down strums on each big chord picture and one down strum on each little chord pictures.
#2 =  Four down strums on each big chord picture and two down strum on each little chord pictures.
#3 = Syncopated strum within the video (listen closely for it...has a triplet feel)]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-doobie-brothers-listen-to-the-music/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anthony Hamilton - Freedom]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/anthony-hamilton-freedom/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[From the motion picture Django Unchained
Performed by Anthony Hamilton & Elayna Boynton.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/anthony-hamilton-freedom/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Los Panchos - Bésame Mucho]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/los-panchos-bésame-mucho/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Besame Mucho on the ukulele by Los Panchos. The chords used are Em Am E7 B A D C7 G G+ E6.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/los-panchos-bésame-mucho/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Niños Tres - Burrito Sabanero]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/niños-tres-burrito-sabanero/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[▶ Check out my gear on Kit: https://kit.com/AndyRamos

This tutorial will show you how to play Mi Burrito Sabanero on the ukulele by Niños Tres. The chords used are G C D B A Em. Song is very syncopated so follow the bass line.

Strum - Easy DDDD, Moderate D DU D DU (emphasize the Up)

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/niños-tres-burrito-sabanero/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Rea - The Road to Hell, Pt. 2]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/chris-rea-the-road-to-hell,-pt.-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Performed & written by Chris Rea.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/chris-rea-the-road-to-hell,-pt.-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elle King - Ex's & Oh's]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/elle-king-ex's-&-oh's/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This video was created by the SUNY Fredonia Ukulele Club and is for educational purposes ONLY.

All rights belong to Elle King and Dave Bassett.

CHORDS USED: A, B, B7, C, D, Em, G

Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/fredoniaukuleleclub/

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/fredoniaukuleleclub/?ref=aymt_homepage_panel

Strum on!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/elle-king-ex's-&-oh's/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ziv Zaifman - A Million Dreams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ziv-zaifman-a-million-dreams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The video is for educational purposes only.  I do not own the rights.
Music by Benj Pasek and Justin Paul]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ziv-zaifman-a-million-dreams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>