<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » F♯7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Chord » F♯7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 15:00:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea Baritone Ukulele Play Along - Baritone Ukulele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/between-the-devil-and-the-deep-blue-sea-baritone-ukulele-play-along-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Keys of G and B.

Chords Used: G, Em, Am, D7, G7, C, Cm, D+, B, Abm, C#m, F#7, A, F, Eb7, C#dim, Em7

Original performance by George Harrison

Our local ukulele group is working on this song, and I was asked to check out the chords they are using (and the tablature they are using), and I made a play along video (there is no tablature in this song).

Tutorial Video (History, GCEA chords, & strumming) on the sister channel (please subscribe!): https://youtu.be/8bll9-iQLW8

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

Interested in UkeStuff merchandise?  https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

You are invited to visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/between-the-devil-and-the-deep-blue-sea-baritone-ukulele-play-along-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Caspar Babypants - Always Keep a Ukulele in Your Trunk - Baritone Ukulele - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/caspar-babypants-always-keep-a-ukulele-in-your-trunk-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of A.

As performed by Caspar Babypants (Chris Ballew), used with permission!  (Thanks, Caspar Babypants!)

The image for the video comes from the Kala Brand Instruments website (Kala Ukuleles).

On babypantsmusic.com, Caspar Babypants describes the inspiration for this song:

"I was watching a documentary about George Harrison and in that documentary Tom Petty told a story about George coming to his house to give him a ukulele. George and Tom strolled through the garden playing ukuleles having a grand old time. When George went to leave he asked Tom if he wanted more ukuleles. Tom said he was okay with one ukulele but George insisted and opened the trunk of his car to reveal a HUGE pile of ukuleles. The moment Tom Petty finished telling the story I realized I had to write a song about this incredible moment. I think it's good advice to always keep a ukulele within arms reach! You never know when you need to elevate your mood with the sparkly sound of a uke."

This song is much easier to play on a baritone ukulele than on a soprano/concert/tenor ukulele.

Tutorial video for GCEA ukulele: https://youtu.be/s6Q0aXQq_Eg

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/caspar-babypants-always-keep-a-ukulele-in-your-trunk-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Caspar Babypants - Always Keep a Ukulele in Your Trunk - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/caspar-babypants-always-keep-a-ukulele-in-your-trunk-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of A.

As performed by Caspar Babypants (Chris Ballew), used with permission!  (Thanks, Caspar Babypants!)

The image for the video comes from the Kala Brand Instruments website (Kala Ukuleles).

On babypantsmusic.com, Caspar Babypants describes the inspiration for this song:

"I was watching a documentary about George Harrison and in that documentary Tom Petty told a story about George coming to his house to give him a ukulele. George and Tom strolled through the garden playing ukuleles having a grand old time. When George went to leave he asked Tom if he wanted more ukuleles. Tom said he was okay with one ukulele but George insisted and opened the trunk of his car to reveal a HUGE pile of ukuleles. The moment Tom Petty finished telling the story I realized I had to write a song about this incredible moment. I think it's good advice to always keep a ukulele within arms reach! You never know when you need to elevate your mood with the sparkly sound of a uke."

I really like this song for a number of reasons.  First, it pays tribute to George Harrison, one of the Beatles.  The song also pays tribute in its actual sound, which is reminiscent (to me) to "Yellow Submarine."  Second, the song is about ukuleles.  Finally, the song offers some opportunities to stretch your playing ability with some more difficult chords (C#min, F#7) and some fingerpicking.

Tutorial video for GCEA ukulele: https://youtu.be/s6Q0aXQq_Eg

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/caspar-babypants-always-keep-a-ukulele-in-your-trunk-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Josh Groban - Believe - Baritone Ukulele - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/josh-groban-believe-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of D.  Lowered from the original key of E.

As performed by Josh Groban.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/josh-groban-believe-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Josh Groban - Believe - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/josh-groban-believe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of D.  Lowered from the original key of E.

As performed by Josh Groban.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/josh-groban-believe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Puth - Done for Me - Key of Bm]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/charlie-puth-done-for-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Done For Me by Charlie Puth featuring Kehlani on the ukulele. The chords used are Bm7 Abdim7 Gmaj7 C#m7 F#7.

*The Abdim7 should be G#dim7 but I couldn't find the diagram in the chord font I use. Had to use the enharmonic.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/charlie-puth-done-for-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lea Salonga - A Whole New World - Key of D, F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lea-salonga-a-whole-new-world/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Keys of D and F...18 chords in all!  I was originally considering changing the key...but the original key is about as ukulele friendly as you are going to find, even with some expanded chords.  I think these chords work better than most of the written chord charts you will find for this song on the Internet.  Enjoy!

As performed in Aladdin!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lea-salonga-a-whole-new-world/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[La La Land Cast - Another Day Of Sun - Key of G, G#]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/la-la-land-cast-another-day-of-sun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  In the Key of G and G#.  There are fifteen chords in all.  These are listed on the second screen of the video.

The original song is in Ab and A...and it becomes much easier to play in F.  However, the original audio becomes strange if the pitch is modified that much.  Therefore, I dropped the audio a half step to G...resulting in this play along.

The last section modulates a half step...this is pretty easy to do with the barre chords provided.  That said...you need to be ready for them.

This is not a ukulele play along for beginners...but it is a great song, and advanced players should have some play along videos that challenge them, too!

The original video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lV5XmoWC8Mo

The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education available from ukefarm.com.  I did have to manually create some of the second position barre chords for the video (the text and chords were prepared in Keynote)]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/la-la-land-cast-another-day-of-sun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley - Blue Hawaii - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/elvis-presley-blue-hawaii-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Key of G: A7, Hawaiian D7, G, Cm, E7, G7, D, D+.  The D+ is an uncommon chord..make sure to practice it before starting the song!

This is in the original Key of A.  There is also a version in the lowered key of G available.

The original YouTube video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p2h0f1VgDrM

The ukulele font comes from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/elvis-presley-blue-hawaii-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>