<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Theme</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Theme</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 15:44:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pismo Ukulele Theme Song Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/pismo-ukulele-theme-song-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F, as performed by Pismo from Pismo Ukulele (on YouTube).

Special thanks to Pismo for the short video clip in the middle of the play along.

I can’t tell you how much I enjoy Pismo.  I look forward to each and e every new episode on a Thursday.  If I have to explain it, you just won’t understand...but be assured that Pismo isn’t making fun of the ukulele community, and don’t take yourself too seriously.

As performed by Pismo

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS and DR Multi-Color ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/pismo-ukulele-theme-song-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Game of Thrones Theme Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/game-of-thrones-theme-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Keys of Cm and C.

Published a couple of days before the beginning of Season 7 of Game of Thrones.  This show is not for kids, but the theme song is fantastic and they have probably heard it.  Follow the chords (the Ab is tricky as a barre chord, but it comes pretty naturally after a Cm), and there is an optional picking part for the last 4 measure.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/game-of-thrones-theme-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ray Parker Jr. - Ghostbusters]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ray-parker-jr-ghostbusters/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Modified and optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of A.

As performed by Ray Parker, Jr

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ray-parker-jr-ghostbusters/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>