<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » Cm</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Cm</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 22:55:35 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Grace VanderWaal - Escape My Mind]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/grace-vanderwaal-escape-my-mind/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Escape My Mind - Grace VanderWaal

Using the chords: C  Cm  Em  G

Suggested Strum Patterns: DU DU DU DU
Note play du DU du DU - captials have more accent


This video is meant for educational purposes and ukulele lessons.

No copyright infringement intended.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/grace-vanderwaal-escape-my-mind/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Taron Egerton - I'm Still Standing ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/taron-egerton-i'm-still-standing/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Cm and C.  Raised a whole step from the original (Bbm and Bb).  This is an updated video, just for the intro slide and the description.  Sadly, you cannot update a video with a new version on YouTube.  I left a link to this video on the original video.

As performed by Taron Egerton in “Sing.”  I had originally had Taron Egerton's name wrong, and a number of people wrote comments to complain about it.

My boys enjoyed Sing and frequently sing this song.  I had started working on but moved on to other videos.  Katie Denure (One Music School) posted a tutorial today (https://youtu.be/m_Xoe9g00oc), which inspired me to wrap up this video.  I took away some of the fast Ab Bb C changes that occur at the end of some phrases...feel free to add them back in your own practice.  This video offers some good Barre chord practice (partial and full) with Cm, Ab, and Bb.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Visit the sister ukulele channel to this channel, YouTube.com/ukestuff]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/taron-egerton-i'm-still-standing/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Clapton - Tears in Heaven]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/eric-clapton-tears-in-heaven/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: F, C, Dm Bb, A, Gm, Cm, D, C7

Tears in Heaven by Eric Clapton.  This version does not have the bridge.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones to the key of C so beginner ukulele students can play along.  Some of the more complex chords have been simplified or skipped.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/eric-clapton-tears-in-heaven/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dawn - Tie a Yellow Ribbon Round the Ole Oak Tree]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dawn-tie-a-yellow-ribbon-round-the-ole-oak-tree/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Performed by Tony Orlando & Dawn
Written by Irwin Levine & L. Russel Brown]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dawn-tie-a-yellow-ribbon-round-the-ole-oak-tree/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Duplessis - Lemonade - Alex Boye]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/jerry-duplessis-lemonade---alex-boye/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Lemonade on the ukulele by Alex Boye. The chords used are G C D B7 Cm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/jerry-duplessis-lemonade---alex-boye/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Bublé - Someday ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-bublé-someday/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Someday on the ukulele by Michael Bublé and Meghan Trainor. The chords used are G C D Am Em7 plus an optional Uke 2 part that uses A B Cm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-bublé-someday/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Guaraldi Trio - Linus and Lucy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/vince-guaraldi-trio-linus-and-lucy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Linus and Lucy on the ukulele by The Vince Guaraldi Trio. The chords used are C F G Cm. Original in Ab.

*This is an edited version that repeats the main theme and takes out the rest of the song. This is NOT the full version.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/vince-guaraldi-trio-linus-and-lucy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Seville - Christmas Don't Be Late]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/david-seville-christmas-don't-be-late/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by The Chipmunks.

I have heard this several times since Thanksgiving.  Time to make a play along!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/david-seville-christmas-don't-be-late/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood with The Stockland Green Bilateral School First Year Choir - I Wish It Could Be Christmas Everyday]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/roy-wood-with-the-stockland-green-bilateral-school-first-year-choir-i-wish-it-could-be-christmas-everyday/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along - Xmas

I Wish It Could Be Christmas Everyday - Wizzard
by Roy Wood


Using the chords: A  A7  Am  Bb  Cm  D  Dm  Em  F  G  G7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU or D DU U DU



This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/roy-wood-with-the-stockland-green-bilateral-school-first-year-choir-i-wish-it-could-be-christmas-everyday/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake - Say Something]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/justin-timberlake-say-something/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  In the original key of Cm.

As performed by Justin Timberlake and Chris Stapleton.

Thanks to Katie Wardrobe, from Midnight Music (www.midnightmusic.com.au) for suggesting this song.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/justin-timberlake-say-something/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>