<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » D♯Dim</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » D♯Dim</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 01:58:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Randy Newman - You've Got a Friend in Me]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/randy-newman-you-ve-got-a-friend-in-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Lowered a minor third from the original.

As performed by Randy Newman.

I have wanted to arrange this for some time.  Another video play along showed chords that didn’t match the music (!).  Randy Newman is incredible, and the original chords are tough on ukulele.  I lowered the key to make it work better for ukulele, and there are some chords that I chose that work—but are definitely not the original chord (D#dim and Dm in the intro).  That said, these chords work with the recording—and could be taken away from the recording and performed live.  I might make a chord sheet for this one.

Dedicated to my friend and college roommate, David, who loved Toy Story.  Incidentally, one of my sons is named Andy and had both Woody and Buzz (we didn’t name him after Toy Story...going for the full name “Andrew”)

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/randy-newman-you-ve-got-a-friend-in-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blackbird - The Beatles - Uke Play-Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/blackbird-the-beatles-uke-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Not for the faint of heart. This is a tough one.  Lots of interesting chords, which is unusual for my channel because I try to stay to about 6 basic chords.  Chords are G, Am7, D, C, A7, D#dim, Em, G-aug, A9, Cm, D7, Gm7, Dm, F.  Is that enough for ya?  ;)

When there are single chords in a row...I'd suggest beginning by just doing one down strum for each chord (that will help you switch).  When there is more than chord in a row, you might try a D- DU kind of shuffling strum.  Once you've got the chords going, just listen to the recording and the strumming that feels good.

People requested a version of Blackbird that was slower to help them get up to speed for the original version.  I created a version at 70% speed, 80% speed, and 90% speed.

Find the version of Blackbird at 70% tempo at https://youtu.be/KquusSdT6OE

Find the version of Blackbird at 80% tempo at https://youtu.be/EmEa-4NhP5I

Find the version of Blackbird at 90% tempo at https://youtu.be/b9Q5FzAy8fs]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/blackbird-the-beatles-uke-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>