<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Naomi Scott</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Naomi Scott</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 23:44:06 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Naomi Scott - Speechless]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/naomi-scott-speechless/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for CGEA ukulele.  Key of Em.

Chords Used: Em, D7, C, D, G, Bsus4, B, Am, Bm7

Original performance by Naomi Scott, from the (2019) motion picture "Aladdin"

Earlier today, I had posted a version of this without the "follow the chord boxes."  I'm not quite sure where they went, as I start with the ukulele version and then move to other versions.  So, I have re-uploaded the video.  Sorry for any inconvenience.

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature only video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (GCEA chords & Strumming/Finger Picking): https://youtu.be/aH4_OQ2pNiI

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/naomi-scott-speechless/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>