<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Holiday (Religious)</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Holiday (Religious)</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:36:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Easter Egg Hunt by KizCastle -  Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/easter-egg-hunt-by-kizcastle-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

The pitch has been lowered to make it playable by young ukulele students.

Source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rov5t-aggeQ

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/easter-egg-hunt-by-kizcastle-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Angels We Have Heard on High (Wilson) Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/angels-we-have-heard-on-high-wilson-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G. There is a key change in the original; I have modified the file to remain in G.

As performed by Josh Wilson.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/angels-we-have-heard-on-high-wilson-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>