<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Anne Janelle</title>
    <link>http://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Anne Janelle</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 02:15:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anne Janelle - Angels We Have Heard on High]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/anne-janelle-angels-we-have-heard-on-high/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  A new melody to the traditional Christmas Carol (and a new verse).
Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Transposed up to the Key of C.  Want a challenge?  Try it in the original key (https://youtu.be/yAvwmn22qTY)

As performed by Anne Janelle with James Hill.  Anne Janelle is a singer and cello player, and is married to ukulele virtuoso and ukulele educator James Hill.  Anne released this song this week--and released a handwritten chart of the chords of the song today, inviting people to play along.  As it is Christmas Day, this will be the last Christmas/holiday play along that I create in 2018.

If you are new to the channel and/or ukulele, you can find all kinds of play along videos like these, which allow you to play along with the music you already know and love--sometimes modified to be in more ukulele friendly keys.  There are also a number of great ukulele instructors on YouTube, including Cynthia Lin, Kate DeNure (One Music School), John Atkins (The Ukulele Teacher), Mike Lynch (who passed away in January of 2018, but his many videos are still out there to learn from), Stu Fuchs, Aldrine Guerrero (Ukulele Underground) and more.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/anne-janelle-angels-we-have-heard-on-high/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>