<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Barenaked Ladies</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Barenaked Ladies</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 13:17:28 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barenaked Ladies - If I Had $1,000,000]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/barenaked-ladies-if-i-had-1000000/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Transposed down a whole step from the original.

As performed by the Barenaked Ladies.

The first video play along I created was published on February 15, 2017 was "If I Had a Million Dollars."  https://youtu.be/HgiIcjZWGhw.  Over the last two years, I have created over 350 play along files (and well over 600 videos).  While this song isn't my favorite song, I liked it, and since I have changed how I make videos over these past two years (originally on my Mac, then on my iPad) I wanted to re-make that first video.  I also created a version in the original key (a little tricky for ukulele) and Baritone version as well.

Recently the Barenaked Ladies performed with Melanie Doane and her ukulele program in Toronto, which adds another ukulele to this song (not directly, but with the group).  https://youtu.be/rsmnykNk-4I

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/barenaked-ladies-if-i-had-1000000/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barenaked Ladies - God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/barenaked-ladies-god-rest-ye-merry-gentlemen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Dm.

As performed by The Barenaked Ladies (Featuring Sarah McLachlan)

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/barenaked-ladies-god-rest-ye-merry-gentlemen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barenaked Ladies - I Have A Little Dreidel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/barenaked-ladies-i-have-a-little-dreidel/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G (Original Key)

As performed by the Barenaked Ladies.  I do have another version of this song in C...but this version is fun...and short!

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS ukulele strings.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/barenaked-ladies-i-have-a-little-dreidel/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>