<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » A Firm Handshake</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » A Firm Handshake</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 13:14:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Firm Handshake - Clouds]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/a-firm-handshake-clouds/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Created with letter names so any non-transposing instrument can play along.  Key of C (Lowered a Whole Step from the Original Key).

As performed by Zach Sobiech.

I have an older version of this video, but a member of the Facebook Ukulele Video Play Along Group requested a version in a different key, so I created videos of the song in several version.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/a-firm-handshake-clouds/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>