<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » Em7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Em7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:01:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Brown - Joe Brown - I'll See You In My Dreams - Jools Holland - 2008_UGC]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/joe-brown-joe-brown-i-ll-see-you-in-my-dreams-jools-holland-2008-ugc/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[**NOT FOR BEGINNERS**

I'll See You In My Dreams by Joe Brown And The Bruvvers.  For educational use.  Chords Used: A7, Am, Bb, Bb6, Bb6-2, Bbm6, Bbmaj7, C, C7, Cm6, Cmaj7, D, D7, D7-2, D7(HI), D9, Dm, E7, E7-2, Edim, Em7, F, F/C, F6, F6-5, F7, Fmaj7, G7 (yes, this song uses 28 chords).  The video is from YouTuber Elisa M. and may be found at https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VWERLNXIZGc.  The chord progressions I used were heavily inspired by Jim’s Ukulele Songbook, which may be found at https://ozbcoz.com/Songs/downloadpdf.php?ID=3748%2Csongbook&fbclid=IwAR2UAs9814iikntmCk_pnDdsa9bE964sFKWluY5DTEEr4dIH5qDr2sdSB50 .

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/joe-brown-joe-brown-i-ll-see-you-in-my-dreams-jools-holland-2008-ugc/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[LeAnn Rimes - How Do I Live]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/leann-rimes-how-do-i-live/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: C, G, F, Em7, Asus, A, F-sharp-m, Bm7, Gsus, Dm

“How Do I Live?” by LeAnn Rimes.  It’s been lowered by 2 semitones so inexperienced ukulele players can play along.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/leann-rimes-how-do-i-live/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andie Case - Complicated]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/andie-case-complicated/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Lowered slightly from the Nightcore original.

Chords Used: G, Em, C, D, Dsus4, Em7, Am7

Original Performance by Avril Lavigne; Nightcore version by Andy Case.

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature all video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (GCEA chords & Strumming/Finger Picking): https://youtu.be/-z6dC9kb7Og

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from newlifechurch.tv/resources/motion-backgrounds

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/andie-case-complicated/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes - If I Can't Have You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/shawn-mendes-if-i-can-t-have-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play If I Can’t Have You on the ukulele by Shawn Mendes. The chords used are G Em7 F#m Bm7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/shawn-mendes-if-i-can-t-have-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Bublé - Someday]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-buble-someday/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Someday on the ukulele by Michael Bublé and Meghan Trainor. The chords used are G C D Am Em7 plus an optional Uke 2 part that uses A B Cm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-buble-someday/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Queen Naija - Butterflies]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/queen-naija-butterflies/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Butterflies on the ukulele by The Queen Naija. The chords used are Gmaj7 Dmaj7 Em7 F#m.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/queen-naija-butterflies/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lady Gaga - Shallow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/lady-gaga-shallow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/lady-gaga-shallow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter - Light One Candle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/peter-light-one-candle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Peter, Paul, and Mary.

This tune is a favorite song of the Twin Cities Ukulele Club.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/peter-light-one-candle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Spaniels - Goodnight Sweetheart]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-spaniels-goodnight-sweetheart/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by The Spaniels.

They played this at a baseball game I was at last night (St. Paul Saints).  A nice slow progression of chords in G (and some nice “color” chords as well.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-spaniels-goodnight-sweetheart/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Los Panchos - Sabor a Mi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/los-panchos-sabor-a-mi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Sabor A Mí by Edyie Gormé and Los Panchos on the ukulele. The chords used are D Gmaj7 C7 Fdim7 Em7 A D7 E7 Gm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/los-panchos-sabor-a-mi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>