<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Anna Kendrick</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Anna Kendrick</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 23:21:40 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick - True Colors - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-true-colors-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play True Colors on the ukulele by Anna Kendrick and Justin Timberlake. The chords used are G C D Em B7. Original in Key E.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-true-colors-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick - True Colors - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-true-colors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play True Colors on the ukulele by Anna Kendrick and Justin Timberlake. The chords used are C F G Am E7. Original Key is E.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-true-colors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick - When I'm Gone - Universal Pictures Film Music - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-when-i-m-gone-universal-pictures-film-music/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Cups (When I'm Gone) on the ukulele by Anna Kendrick. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Fm

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-when-i-m-gone-universal-pictures-film-music/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick - When I'm Gone - Universal Pictures Film Music - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-when-i-m-gone-universal-pictures-film-music-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Anna Kendrick.

This song was first put to a ukulele play along by Dr. A  (https://youtu.be/JGI1LWfFIZQ).    I have worried about the “Whiskey” line in the past, but I am not worrying about it any more (in a live performance I might substitute “root beer” for students).  I wanted a version without the long cup sequence of the official “Cups” video (students were banging on their ukuleles) and to bring the common look that is shared by most of my videos.  The use of colored strings and Color Chord (plus the cups in the video) was a bonus.

The song has banjo and ukulele.  The ukulele adds an Fm in the final harmonic sequence...but this is being kept to four chords for beginners.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS and DR Multi-Color ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-when-i-m-gone-universal-pictures-film-music-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick - Get Back Up Again - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-get-back-up-again/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-get-back-up-again/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick - When I'm Gone - Universal Pictures Film Music - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-when-i-m-gone-universal-pictures-film-music-3/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Key of C
Chords used:  C  F  Am  G
Three options for strumming
The Bridge section includes an opportunity to use your uke as a percussion instrument or you can improvise a melody using C--D--E--G--A--C'.

I do not own the copyright to this music.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/anna-kendrick-when-i-m-gone-universal-pictures-film-music-3/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>