<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Movie</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Movie</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:16:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[You're The One That I Want - Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/you-re-the-one-that-i-want-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

You're The One That I Want
John Travolta and Olivia Newton-John
From the film - GREASE

Using the chords: Am  C  E7  Em  F  G

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU or D DU UDU
Try doubling the strum speed once you can play it confidently.


This video is meant for educational purposes and ukulele lessons.

No copyright infringement intended.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/you-re-the-one-that-i-want-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Various Artists - The Window Cleaner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/various-artists-the-window-cleaner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

When I'm Cleaning Windows (In C) - George Formby

Using the chords: A7  C  C7  Cdim7  D7  E7  F  G  G7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU DU DU

Notes:
This is a higher key than our other version.

This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/various-artists-the-window-cleaner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beyoncé - SPIRIT]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/beyonce-spirit/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Chords Used: G D Em C B7 Am F

Spirit (from Disney’s The Lion King) by Beyoncé.  It’s been raised by 2 semitones and the modulation has been removed so beginner ukulele students can play along.  Also, the “quick change” chords have not been included.  As for the B7 chord, feel free to do it 432X instead of using the barre.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/beyonce-spirit/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Naomi Scott - Speechless]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/naomi-scott-speechless/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for CGEA ukulele.  Key of Em.

Chords Used: Em, D7, C, D, G, Bsus4, B, Am, Bm7

Original performance by Naomi Scott, from the (2019) motion picture "Aladdin"

Earlier today, I had posted a version of this without the "follow the chord boxes."  I'm not quite sure where they went, as I start with the ukulele version and then move to other versions.  So, I have re-uploaded the video.  Sorry for any inconvenience.

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature only video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (GCEA chords & Strumming/Finger Picking): https://youtu.be/aH4_OQ2pNiI

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/naomi-scott-speechless/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anthony Gonzalez - Un Poco Loco]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/anthony-gonzalez-un-poco-loco/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Un Poco Loco on the ukulele by Anthony Gonzalez and Gael Garcia Bernal. The chords used are G C D A D E.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/anthony-gonzalez-un-poco-loco/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Williams - Star Wars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/john-williams-star-wars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[In honor of today, 4/4/2019 being Star Wars...

This tutorial will show you how to play Star Wars (main theme) by John Williams. The chords used are C F G.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/john-williams-star-wars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shallow (Doebler)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/shallow-doebler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Play along with Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga.
Chords needed: A, Am, Bm, C, D, Em, G]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/shallow-doebler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Owl City - When Can I See You Again?]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/owl-city-when-can-i-see-you-again/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play When Can I See You Again on the ukulele by Owl City. The chords used are C F G Am Dm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

▶ Check out my gear on Kit: https://kit.com/AndyRamos]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/owl-city-when-can-i-see-you-again/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Harris - The Bare Necessities]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/phil-harris-the-bare-necessities/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Original Key.

From the Jungle Book.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/phil-harris-the-bare-necessities/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Christopher Walken - I Wan'na Be Like You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/christopher-walken-i-wan-na-be-like-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

I Wan'na Be Like You - The Jungle Book (2016 version)
As sung by Christopher Walken
Walt Disney Films

Using the chords: Am  A7  C  D7  E7  G7


Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU or D DU DU DU

This version has been altered with the pitch being made more suitable for ukulele chords and the instrumental section in the middle of the song cut short.


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/christopher-walken-i-wan-na-be-like-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>