<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Musical</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Musical</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 15:08:40 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Original Broadway Cast of Hamilton - Satisfied - Key of Am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/original-broadway-cast-of-hamilton-satisfied/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Satisfied from Hamilton.  It’s been lowered by 3 semitones so beginner ukulele players can play along.  Chord used: Am, D, F, and E7.  The lyric video was created and posted by YouTuber LyricsBy Allie, I simply added the chords.  The simplified chords were inspired by YouTuber Cory Teaches Music.  For educational use.

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/original-broadway-cast-of-hamilton-satisfied/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Memory from "Cats" - Ukulele Play Along - Key of A, C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/memory-from-cats-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: A, F-sharp minor, D, C-sharp minor, Bm, E, F#, B, F, Dm, Bb, Am, G, C, Em (Starts in the key of A, ends in the key of C).

Memory from the musical “Cats” by Andrew Lloyd Webber.  It’s been lowered by 1 semitone so beginner ukulele students can play along.  I just added chords to the lyric video created by YouTuber
Miyanoe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/memory-from-cats-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Platt - Waving Through A Window - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ben-platt-waving-through-a-window/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

Chords Used: C, F(add9), Gsus4, Am, Dm, G, F, E7

From Dear Evan Hansen

See the tutorial video (GCEA) at https://youtu.be/jPyNJ7l_T_A

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for GCEA ukulele, available at ukefarm.com. The Motion background video is from pixasbay.com (window-billlowing-curtains-drapes-1000)

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ben-platt-waving-through-a-window/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Time Warp - Ukulele Play Along - Rocky Horror Show - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-time-warp-ukulele-play-along-rocky-horror-show/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

The Time Warp - The Rocky Horror Picture Show
Written by Richard O'Brien
Original Roxy Cast - starring Tim Curry

Using the chords: A  B  B7  C  D  E7  F G


Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU

There are part of the song which would benefit from different strum patterns to make it more interesting
eg. DU DU U U DUDU at the very start


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-time-warp-ukulele-play-along-rocky-horror-show/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Israel Kamakawiwo'ole - What A Wonderful World - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/israel-kamakawiwo-ole-what-a-wonderful-world-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Performed by Israel Kamakawiwo'ole.
Written by Harold Arlen & E.Y. Harburg / George David Weiss & Bob Thiele & Israel Kamakawiwo'ole

The ukulele song for me and I guess for countless others. It got me into uke playing so I wanted to make a easy-to-follow version for other Iz fans out there.

The picture is of young Iz. I don't have the info of the photographer but I hope they will not mind me using it here. Iz has gone behind the rainbow long ago but I can't help wondering if he, as a kid or even later on in his life, ever dreamed of becoming the much loved artist he grew up to be.

I wanted to make a version where you can follow either chord markings in the text of the regular ones at the bottom of the video (or both).

For strumming help, see this helpful video from the wonderful Cynthia Lin: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qqDiaZ-pqyA

Note: The rather complicated Dm7 can be played as a regular Dm as well.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/israel-kamakawiwo-ole-what-a-wonderful-world-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ziv Zaifman - A Million Dreams - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ziv-zaifman-a-million-dreams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As heard in The Greatest Showman.

Also visit the version by Kris Gilbert: https://youtu.be/0_auBl2YMEQ

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ziv-zaifman-a-million-dreams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jonathan Groff - You'll Be Back - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/jonathan-groff-you-ll-be-back/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

From Hamilton.

The Copyright Holders just allowed publication of this video!  Thank you!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/jonathan-groff-you-ll-be-back/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charmian Carr - Edelweiss - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charmian-carr-edelweiss/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Lowered a half step from the original. The introduction from the original has also been removed.

From The Sound of Music.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/charmian-carr-edelweiss/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Connie Fisher - Do-Re-Mi - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/connie-fisher-do-re-mi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  This is the full version of the song.  For the short version go to: https://youtu.be/EjVLkIhrO0s

From the Sound of Music

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/connie-fisher-do-re-mi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Connie Fisher - Do-Re-Mi - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/connie-fisher-do-re-mi-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  This is a shortened version.  For the full version, go to this video: https://youtu.be/UuEgqX51fuM

From The Sound of Music

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/connie-fisher-do-re-mi-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>