<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Gene Autry</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Gene Autry</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 19:28:08 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gene Autry - Back in the Saddle Again]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/gene-autry-back-in-the-saddle-again/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Gene Autry.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/gene-autry-back-in-the-saddle-again/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gene Autry - Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/gene-autry-rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Keys of G and C.

As performed by Gene Autry

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/gene-autry-rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gene Autry - Here Comes Santa Claus ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/gene-autry-here-comes-santa-claus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Best with GCEA tuned ukuleles (due to embedded chord charts). Key of C.  The second part of the melody has a fast chord progression...it is suggested that you practice it separately.

The original version was in C# (!), so the audio has been lowered a half step.  The full version has a quick modulation to G, and a couple of verses that refer to Christianity.  For the sake of public schools, these have been removed in this version.  If you want to play the modulation and sing all the verses, please use the full version (link: https://youtu.be/3rbEFcHRrbM)

Created on an iPad with Luma Fusion, iCab Mobile. Twisted Wave, and Any Font.  The ukulele chord font is a part of Chordette for Education which can be found at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/gene-autry-here-comes-santa-claus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>