<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Sam Smith</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Sam Smith</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 21:45:16 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Smith - Too Good At Goodbyes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-smith-too-good-at-goodbyes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Dm

Chords Used: Dm, F, C, Gm

As performed by Sam Smith

This video has been blocked by the copyright holder since it was published on December 1, 2017.  The copyright holder is now allowing it to be used (thank you!) so it is available to you!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-smith-too-good-at-goodbyes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Smith - Dancing With a Stranger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-smith-dancing-with-a-stranger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use ...Key transposed to play the chords of C, D, Em, and G]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-smith-dancing-with-a-stranger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>