<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Bryant Oden</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Bryant Oden</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 15:00:24 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryant Oden - I Got A Pea - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bryant-oden-i-got-a-pea/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play I Got A Pea on the ukulele by Bryant Oden Songdrops.com. The chords used are C F G Am.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bryant-oden-i-got-a-pea/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryant Oden - I Love U...kuleles - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bryant-oden-i-love-u-kuleles/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Bryant Oden.  Used with permission!  See his work at songdrops.com, and also subscribe to his YouTube channel (https://www.youtube.com/user/songdrops).

Dedicated to my wife; we just celebrated our 12th anniversary...and she was in India, working at a children’s home, and I was at home, working on ukulele videos (and taking care of our boys).

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bryant-oden-i-love-u-kuleles/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryant Oden - I Love U...kuleles - Baritone Ukulele - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bryant-oden-i-love-u-kuleles-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of A.

As performed by Bryant Oden.  Used with permission!  See his work at songdrops.com, and also subscribe to his YouTube channel (https://www.youtube.com/user/songdrops).

Dedicated to my wife; we just celebrated our 12th anniversary...and she was in India, working at a children’s home, and I was at home, working on ukulele videos (and taking care of our boys).

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bryant-oden-i-love-u-kuleles-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>