<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Hank Williams</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Hank Williams</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 15:01:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Jambalaya - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

Chords Used: C, G7

As performed by Hank Williams.

Dr. Reese has had a video of this available for a long time, but the original recording was in a different tuning.  This version has been adjusted to A440.

This video was also blocked on YouTube since it was published (Feb 2, 2019), but the copyright holders recently removed the restrictions on the video.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Jambalaya - Baritone Ukulele - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of C.

Chords Used: C, G7

As performed by Hank Williams.

Dr. Reese has had a video of this available for a long time, but the original recording was in a different tuning.  This version has been adjusted to A440.

This video was also blocked on YouTube since it was published (Feb 2, 2019), but the copyright holders recently removed the restrictions on the video.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Ain't Misbehavin' - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-ain-t-misbehavin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Ain’t Misbehavin’ on the ukulele by Hank Williams Jr. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Em Fm A7 C7 D7 E7 G7 .

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-ain-t-misbehavin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Lovesick Blues - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-lovesick-blues/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F.

As performed by Hank Williams.  Mason Ramsey has brought this song to prominence again (Wal-Mart Yodeling Boy) and you or your students may enjoy playing/yodeling along.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-lovesick-blues/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Jambalaya - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chords: C, F, G7]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>