<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » Gm</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Gm</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 19:28:08 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Taron Egerton - I'm Still Standing ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/taron-egerton-i'm-still-standing/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Cm and C.  Raised a whole step from the original (Bbm and Bb).  This is an updated video, just for the intro slide and the description.  Sadly, you cannot update a video with a new version on YouTube.  I left a link to this video on the original video.

As performed by Taron Egerton in “Sing.”  I had originally had Taron Egerton's name wrong, and a number of people wrote comments to complain about it.

My boys enjoyed Sing and frequently sing this song.  I had started working on but moved on to other videos.  Katie Denure (One Music School) posted a tutorial today (https://youtu.be/m_Xoe9g00oc), which inspired me to wrap up this video.  I took away some of the fast Ab Bb C changes that occur at the end of some phrases...feel free to add them back in your own practice.  This video offers some good Barre chord practice (partial and full) with Cm, Ab, and Bb.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Visit the sister ukulele channel to this channel, YouTube.com/ukestuff]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/taron-egerton-i'm-still-standing/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Beach Boys - I Can Hear Music ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-beach-boys-i-can-hear-music/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

I Can Hear Music - The Beach Boys

Using the chords: A  A7  D  D7  Em  F#m  G  Gm

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU or DU DU DU DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-beach-boys-i-can-hear-music/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Johnson - Better Together]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/jack-johnson-better-together/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Better Together - Jack Johnson

Using the chords: A  Bb  C  Dm  F  Gm

Suggested Strum Patterns: DU XU DU XU or DU DU DU DU  (X=chuck)


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/jack-johnson-better-together/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Marry You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Marry You - Bruno Mars

Using the chords: Bb  F  Gm

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU or D DU D DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Clapton - Tears in Heaven]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/eric-clapton-tears-in-heaven/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: F, C, Dm Bb, A, Gm, Cm, D, C7

Tears in Heaven by Eric Clapton.  This version does not have the bridge.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones to the key of C so beginner ukulele students can play along.  Some of the more complex chords have been simplified or skipped.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/eric-clapton-tears-in-heaven/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dawn - Tie a Yellow Ribbon Round the Ole Oak Tree]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dawn-tie-a-yellow-ribbon-round-the-ole-oak-tree/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Performed by Tony Orlando & Dawn
Written by Irwin Levine & L. Russel Brown]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dawn-tie-a-yellow-ribbon-round-the-ole-oak-tree/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Big Mountain - Baby, I Love Your Way]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/big-mountain-baby,-i-love-your-way/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Baby I Love Your Way on the ukulele by Big Mountain. The chords used are F C Bb Dm Am Gm Bbm7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/big-mountain-baby,-i-love-your-way/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Prince Royce - Darte un Beso]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/prince-royce-darte-un-beso/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Darte Un Beso on the ukulele by Prince Royce. The chords used are F C Bb Dm G Gm.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/prince-royce-darte-un-beso/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ciara - Beauty Marks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ciara-beauty-marks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Chords used in this song: F, A7, Gm, Dm, G7, C, B flat, and Am]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ciara-beauty-marks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Smith - Too Good At Goodbyes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-smith-too-good-at-goodbyes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Dm

Chords Used: Dm, F, C, Gm

As performed by Sam Smith

This video has been blocked by the copyright holder since it was published on December 1, 2017.  The copyright holder is now allowing it to be used (thank you!) so it is available to you!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-smith-too-good-at-goodbyes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>