<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Stevie Wonder</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Stevie Wonder</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 16:02:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder - Faith - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/stevie-wonder-faith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Faith on the ukulele by Stevie Wonder and Ariana Grande. The chords used are G7 C7 D7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/stevie-wonder-faith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder - Isn't She Lovely]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/stevie-wonder-isn-t-she-lovely/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Stevie Wonder singing Isn’t She Lovely, with the pitch lowered 4 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.

Perfect for weddings, mother’s day, and all other occasions of love.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/stevie-wonder-isn-t-she-lovely/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder - Faith - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/stevie-wonder-faith-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/stevie-wonder-faith-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>