<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » B♭M7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » B♭M7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 01:42:58 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Universe - We Are the Crystal Gems - Baritone Ukulele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/steven-universe-we-are-the-crystal-gems-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE Ukulele.  Keys of F & G.

Chords Used: F, A7, Bb, C, Bbm, Gm7, Am7, Bbm7, E7, Am, Dm, G, Cmaj7, D7, C7, B7, Cm, Em, Gmaj7

As performed on Steven Universe

Tutorial Video (GCEA & DGBE): https://youtu.be/pdzcOAduI8E

********************
Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.  If you don't have a podcast app, please check out Radio Public for all your podcasts--they support podcasters financially.

You are invited to visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (a free resource).  Also on social media: Twitter (@UkeStuff) and Instagram (@ukestuff.info).

Want to make a donation towards this work?   Visit https://www.paypal.me/ukestuff or https://www.buymeacoffee.com/ukestuff

Check out the "merch": https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/steven-universe-we-are-the-crystal-gems-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Universe - We Are the Crystal Gems - Key of F, G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/steven-universe-we-are-the-crystal-gems/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA Ukulele.  Keys of F & G.

Chords Used: F, A7, Bb, C, Bbm, Gm7, Am7, Bbm7, E7, Am, Dm, G, Cmaj7, D7, C7, B7, Cm, Em, Gmaj7

As performed on Steven Universe

Tutorial Video (GCEA & DGBE): https://youtu.be/pdzcOAduI8E

********************
Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.  If you don't have a podcast app, please check out Radio Public for all your podcasts--they support podcasters financially.

You are invited to visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (a free resource).  Also on social media: Twitter (@UkeStuff) and Instagram (@ukestuff.info).

Want to make a donation towards this work?   Visit https://www.paypal.me/ukestuff or https://www.buymeacoffee.com/ukestuff

Check out the "merch": https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/steven-universe-we-are-the-crystal-gems/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Big Mountain - Baby, I Love Your Way - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/big-mountain-baby-i-love-your-way/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Baby I Love Your Way on the ukulele by Big Mountain. The chords used are F C Bb Dm Am Gm Bbm7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/big-mountain-baby-i-love-your-way/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Withers - Lovely Day - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Lovely Day on the ukulele by Bill Withers. The chords used are F Dm7 Bbmaj7 Bbm7 Cm7 Eb C#maj7(Dbmaj7)

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Perfect Pitch Ukulele Play Along (Updated) - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/perfect-pitch-ukulele-play-along-updated/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.   Chords optimized for CGEA ukulele.   Key of F (C7, F, Am, Dm, Bb, C, Cm7, G7, Bbm7, C#7).  The Bacon Brothers dropped this video on Social Media while on tour.  As of yet, there are no chord arrangements of it yet...but as I celebrate my 30th ukulele play along video this month (30 videos in 30 days...or 22 days), I thought I would do something special.  It is a great song, and there is a wonderful reference to "Ukulele Lady" in the instrumental break.  I included their actual video in the play along...hopefully it isn't too distracting from the chords.  A link to that video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B5vWSIe2GCE

Updated for some spelling errors from the original video; remade on Luma Fusion for iOS.

The material, of course, remains the property of the Bacon Brothers...hopefully they are okay with the play along idea.  In the video, some other versions of some of the chords are used (such as C being played with a barre chord), but I tried to use standard root position chords as much as possible.

The ukulele font is from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/perfect-pitch-ukulele-play-along-updated/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>