<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Ingrid Michaelson</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Ingrid Michaelson</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 14:45:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ingrid Michaelson - The Way I Am - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Ingrid Michaelson.

I watched Autumn Best’s performance of this song this morning (https://youtu.be/ckcZiDhPYSc) and decided to listen to the original recording—this is a wonderful song with some surprising chords along the way.  Kris Gilbert also has a play along of this video, so check out her version, too (https://youtu.be/FDdVhPdIR_E)

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ingrid Michaelson - You And I - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-you-and-i/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C (original key).

As performed by Ingrid Michaelson.

Check the lyrics as this may not be appropriate for use in a school setting (i.e. “do what the bunnies do,” and “spoon.”).

This version Includes some of the color chords (Fadd9) that Ingrid uses but are not on the chord charts you will find on the internet.  For the Gsus4, play a G chord and add the pinky at the same time.

The original leads to a final chorus that is not accompanied by ukulele.  I ended the play along at that point.  Sorry about the chords there..Ingrid switches to Csus4 to C to Csus4 to C at the end and I didn’t want to add yet another slide.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-you-and-i/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ingrid Michaelson - The Way I Am - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Music by Ingrid Michaelson

This video is for educational purposes only.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>