<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Kidz Bop Kids</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Kidz Bop Kids</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:38:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[KIDZ BOP Kids - Party in the USA - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-party-in-the-usa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Raised a half step from the original (Key of F#).

As performed by Miley Cyrus.

A little bit about this song...I have been unable to find songs that I want to make play alongs out of, and much of the current Top 40 (that we haven't already made play along videos for) have explicit lyrics.  Most of the play along videos I create are intended to be able to used in a classroom, and lyrics are a concern.

So I looked at several lists of "Top 100 Pop Songs of All Time" and this song appeared, so I decided to start it, in the Key of G.  As I was wrapping up the first version of the video, I decided to look to see if it had been done already...and it had--very well--by my colleague Andy Ramos (https://youtu.be/TMyrB8iVlOY).  I don't usually re-make videos unless I have another specific goal, so this was a mistake.  Since there isn't a Baritone version, I modified the video for Baritone, and then changed the Key to the Key of F as well (a half step lower than the original).  I noticed that, in F, most of the song, other than the bridge, uses four basic chords (F, Am, Dm, C), so I decided to also add a version that removed the bridge...making the song easier to play than the Key of G on GCEA ukulele (i.e. Bm barre chord).  So in the end, I'm glad I made the song...but didn't mean to copy Andy's work in any way.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-party-in-the-usa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[KIDZ BOP Kids - Shut Up and Dance]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-shut-up-and-dance/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This video is about Shut Up and Dance]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-shut-up-and-dance/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[KIDZ BOP Kids - Uptown Funk - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-uptown-funk/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dm and G chords with picking for the bass line.
For picking practice (70%, 80%, 90%, and original speed) see this video: https://youtu.be/3VArgbquzx4]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-uptown-funk/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[KIDZ BOP Kids - Cake by the Ocean - Key of Em]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-cake-by-the-ocean/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This video is for educational purposes only. I do not own the rights to the music.

Music by DNCE.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/kidz-bop-kids-cake-by-the-ocean/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>