<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » The Von Trapp Children</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » The Von Trapp Children</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:00:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Von Trapp Children - Hot Cup Of Cocoa - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-von-trapp-children-hot-cup-of-cocoa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of D.  Lowered from the original and kept in one key (The original is in Eb and E).  In the intro area, I did not add the suspensions on the D and A7--feel free to add them as you play (if you wish).

As performed by the Von Trapp Children.

This was a request from Marsha Burton Joss on the Facebook Ukulele Video Play Along Group.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-von-trapp-children-hot-cup-of-cocoa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Von Trapp Children - Hot Cup Of Cocoa - Baritone Ukulele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-von-trapp-children-hot-cup-of-cocoa-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of D.  Lowered from the original and kept in one key (The original is in Eb and E).  In the intro area, I did not add the suspensions on the D and A7--feel free to add them as you play (if you wish).

As performed by the Von Trapp Children.

This was a request from Marsha Burton Joss on the Facebook Ukulele Video Play Along Group.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-von-trapp-children-hot-cup-of-cocoa-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>