<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Julia Nui’S Kama’Ainas</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Julia Nui’S Kama’Ainas</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:52:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Julia Nui’s Kama’ainas - On The Beach at Waikiki - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/julia-nuis-kamaainas-on-the-beach-at-waikiki/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Julia Nui's Kama'ainas.

Why would I make this play along?  It turns out this song was written for the Pan Pacific Exhibition in 1915, and this song created the first ukulele craze on the mainland of the United States (and ultimatley the rest of the world).  While there are certainly other historical influences (good and bad) on the ukulele, the instrument would never have taken off as it did without the popularity of this song—and In a round about way, we wouldn’t know about the ukulele today without this song, either.  No, this isn’t in the Top 40 today, but in terms of the Top 40 ukulele songs of all time, this is in the Top 5.

Be ready to play the E-Flat chord.

Background and lyrics taken from the original sheet music for the song: http://digital.library.msstate.edu/utils/getdownloaditem/collection/SheetMusic/id/8571/filename/8572.pdf/mapsto/pdf

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/julia-nuis-kamaainas-on-the-beach-at-waikiki/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Julia Nui’s Kama’ainas - On The Beach at Waikiki - Baritone Ukulele - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/julia-nuis-kamaainas-on-the-beach-at-waikiki-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Julia Nui's Kama'ainas.

Why would I make this play along?  It turns out this song was written for the Pan Pacific Exhibition in 1915, and this song created the first ukulele craze on the mainland of the United States (and ultimatley the rest of the world).  While there are certainly other historical influences (good and bad) on the ukulele, the instrument would never have taken off as it did without the popularity of this song—and In a round about way, we wouldn’t know about the ukulele today without this song, either.  No, this isn’t in the Top 40 today, but in terms of the Top 40 ukulele songs of all time, this is in the Top 5.

Be ready to play the E-Flat chord.  It is easier to transition to the E-Flat chord if you play G with the second finger.

You can also play the “easier” version of A7 (2020)

Background and lyrics taken from the original sheet music for the song: http://digital.library.msstate.edu/utils/getdownloaditem/collection/SheetMusic/id/8571/filename/8572.pdf/mapsto/pdf

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/julia-nuis-kamaainas-on-the-beach-at-waikiki-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>