<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Imagine Dragons</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Imagine Dragons</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 16:23:10 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Bad Liar]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-bad-liar/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.

Chords Used: D, Bm, G, A, F#, Asus4

Key of D, lowered a half step from the original in Eb.

As performed by Imagine Dragons.

Tutorial Video (GCEA): Go to https://youtu.be/cTdAiw4Ox-M

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is based on Chordette for Education (Chordette is available from ukefarm.com, but the baritone font I am using is not yet available from ukefarm).

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-bad-liar/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Whatever It Takes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-whatever-it-takes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Whatever It Takes on the ukulele by Imagine Dragons. The chords used are C F G Em Am D.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-whatever-it-takes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Natural]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-natural/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of Em (Raised a whole step from the original key).

As performed by Imagine Dragons.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Baritone Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-natural/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Thunder]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-thunder/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-thunder/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - On Top Of The World]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-on-top-of-the-world/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play On Top Of The World on the ukulele by Imagine Dragons. The chords used are C F G Dm Am.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-on-top-of-the-world/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Demons]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-demons/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This video was created by the SUNY Fredonia Ukulele Club and is for educational purposes ONLY.

Chords used: D, A, Bm, G

All rights belong to Dan Reynolds, Alex da Kid, Daniel Wayne Sermon, Daniel Platzman, Ben McKee and Josh Mosser.

Follow our Instagram! https://www.instagram.com/fredoniaukuleleclub/

Like our page on Facebook! https://www.facebook.com/fredoniaukuleleclub/?ref=aymt_homepage_panel

Strum On!!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-demons/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Radioactive]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-radioactive/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Am.  The original is in Bm, so this is a whole step lower.

As performed by Imagine Dragons.

There is an existing ukulele play along by Linse Sullivan (https://youtu.be/F_8rsIOlrOo).  I wanted to add a few things for my students.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS and DR Multi-Color ukulele strings.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-radioactive/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons - Believer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-believer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Am.  The original is in A#m (not a great key for ukulele)...so if you want to play the original key, use a capo on the first fret and play these chords.  My boys (age 5 & 9) sing this song all the time (they hear it on the bus on the way to/from school), so I figured it needed to become a play along.  You can experiment with finger picking patterns to match the original guitar.

As performed by Imagine Dragons.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/imagine-dragons-believer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>