<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » C♯7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Chord » C♯7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 23:33:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea Ukulele Play Along - Key of F, A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/between-the-devil-and-the-deep-blue-sea-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for CGEA ukulele.  Keys of F and A.

Chords Used: F, Dm, Gm, C7, F7, Bb, Bbm,, C+, A, F#m, Bm, E7, G, Eb, C#7, Bdim7, Dm7

Original performance by George Harrison

[Corrected Version from the Original Upload]

Our local ukulele group is working on this song, and I was asked to check out the chords they are using (and the tablature they are using), and I made a play along video (there is no tablature in this song).

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature only video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (History, GCEA chords, & strumming) on the sister channel (please subscribe!): https://youtu.be/8bll9-iQLW8

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/between-the-devil-and-the-deep-blue-sea-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea Lyric Based Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/between-the-devil-and-the-deep-blue-sea-lyric-based-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.   Created with letter names so any non-transposing instrument can play along.  Keys of F and A.

Chords Used: F, Dm, Gm, C7, F7, Bb, Bbm,, C+, A, F#m, Bm, E7, G, Eb, C#7, Bdim7, Dm7

Original performance by George Harrison.

Our local ukulele group is working on this song, and I was asked to check out the chords they are using (and the tablature they are using), and I made a play along video (there is no tablature in this song).

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature only video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (History, GCEA chords, & strumming) on the sister channel (please subscribe!): https://youtu.be/8bll9-iQLW8

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.  The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/between-the-devil-and-the-deep-blue-sea-lyric-based-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Jackson - Billie Jean - Key of F#m]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/michael-jackson-billie-jean/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/michael-jackson-billie-jean/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash - Love's Been Good To Me - Key of A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-love-s-been-good-to-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Here's one for those who fancy a little challenge. Tip: play only every second chord. The good thing is, once you master this track you have improved a lot in your uke playing!

Performed by Johnny Cash
Written by Rod McKuen

This video is created for an educational purpose. All rights belong to their respectful owners.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/johnny-cash-love-s-been-good-to-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Perfect Pitch Ukulele Play Along (Updated) - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/perfect-pitch-ukulele-play-along-updated/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.   Chords optimized for CGEA ukulele.   Key of F (C7, F, Am, Dm, Bb, C, Cm7, G7, Bbm7, C#7).  The Bacon Brothers dropped this video on Social Media while on tour.  As of yet, there are no chord arrangements of it yet...but as I celebrate my 30th ukulele play along video this month (30 videos in 30 days...or 22 days), I thought I would do something special.  It is a great song, and there is a wonderful reference to "Ukulele Lady" in the instrumental break.  I included their actual video in the play along...hopefully it isn't too distracting from the chords.  A link to that video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B5vWSIe2GCE

Updated for some spelling errors from the original video; remade on Luma Fusion for iOS.

The material, of course, remains the property of the Bacon Brothers...hopefully they are okay with the play along idea.  In the video, some other versions of some of the chords are used (such as C being played with a barre chord), but I tried to use standard root position chords as much as possible.

The ukulele font is from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/perfect-pitch-ukulele-play-along-updated/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>