<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » Cdim7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Chord » Cdim7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 03:27:10 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Various Artists - The Window Cleaner - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/various-artists-the-window-cleaner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

When I'm Cleaning Windows (In C) - George Formby

Using the chords: A7  C  C7  Cdim7  D7  E7  F  G  G7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU DU DU

Notes:
This is a higher key than our other version.

This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/various-artists-the-window-cleaner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Naomi Scott - Speechless - Baritone Ukulele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/naomi-scott-speechless-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for DGBE ukulele.  Key of Em.

Chords Used: Em, C, D, G, Bsus4, B, Am, Bm7, Cdim7

Original performance by Naomi Scott, from the (2019) motion picture "Aladdin"

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature only video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (GCEA chords & Strumming/Finger Picking): https://youtu.be/aH4_OQ2pNiI

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The baritone ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from motionbolt.com

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/naomi-scott-speechless-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Randy Newman - You've Got a Friend in Me - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/randy-newman-you-ve-got-a-friend-in-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.  Lowered a minor third from the original.

As performed by Randy Newman.

I have wanted to arrange this for some time.  Another video play along showed chords that didn’t match the music (!).  Randy Newman is incredible, and the original chords are tough on ukulele.  I lowered the key to make it work better for ukulele, and there are some chords that I chose that work—but are definitely not the original chord (D#dim and Dm in the intro).  That said, these chords work with the recording—and could be taken away from the recording and performed live.  I might make a chord sheet for this one.

Dedicated to my friend and college roommate, David, who loved Toy Story.  Incidentally, one of my sons is named Andy and had both Woody and Buzz (we didn’t name him after Toy Story...going for the full name “Andrew”)

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/randy-newman-you-ve-got-a-friend-in-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bobby Helms - Jingle Bell Rock - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bobby-helms-jingle-bell-rock/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Best used with GCEA tuned ukuleles.  Key of C.
13 chords (see video).

Chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bobby-helms-jingle-bell-rock/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>