<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Marvin Gaye</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Marvin Gaye</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:01:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marvin Gaye - Ain't No Mountain High Enough]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/marvin-gaye-ain-t-no-mountain-high-enough/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Am.  I have altered the key from the original by a whole step (lower) and minor third (removing a modulation in the song).

As performed by Marvin Gaye and Tammi Terrell.

I heard this a couple of days ago at a St. Paul Saints (independent league) baseball game, and thought about making this play along again.  I had tried in the past, but gave up—it is really hard to get the chords to sound right.  This is my best shot..and I think it works.  There is a quick chord change in the verse...but practice it and you’ll get it.  As mentioned previously, I have lowered the key to Am, and taken away the modulation that happens in the bridge.  Enjoy!

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/marvin-gaye-ain-t-no-mountain-high-enough/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>