<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Traditional</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Traditional</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 16:40:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Twinkle Twinkle Ukulele Play Along - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/twinkle-twinkle-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along of Twinkle Twinkle Little Star
Using the chords: C F and G7

This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/twinkle-twinkle-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The More We Get Together Ukulele Play Along (in C) with KIDS string colors - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-c-with-kids-string-colors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C

There is another version of this video on my channel, as well as versions in another key (F) but I wanted to make this resource available with colored fonts, too.

The colored strings match Aquila KIDS strings.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-c-with-kids-string-colors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The More We Get Together Ukulele Play Along (in F) with KIDS string colors - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-f-with-kids-string-colors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F

There is another version of this video on this channel, as well as versions in another key (C).  I wanted to make this resource available with colored fonts for Aquila KIDS strings.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com. The colored font matches Aquila KIDS ukulele strings.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-f-with-kids-string-colors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tiny Tim - Tip Toe Thru' the Tulips with Me - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/tiny-tim-tip-toe-thru-the-tulips-with-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Optimized for GCEA Ukulele.  Key of C.

In my opinion, two things led to the decline of the ukulele in the late 1960s (continuing until the early 2000s).  The first was the emergence of guitar-based rock (and people wanting to be rock stars), and the image of Tiny Tim.  As part of his "gimmick," Tiny Tim played the ukulele and sang in a weird falsetto, causing an entire generation to associate the ukulele with being a weirdo and maybe even a freak.  When you look deeper at Tiny Tim, he was an accomplished musician but he also knew how to make his mark using a gimmick.

See: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wMbQsKJ64S0

A number of factors led to the re-emergence of the ukulele in the early 2000s, but even today some people have the mental image of Tiny Tim when they think of the ukulele.  I even had a teacher come up to me at a convention and start singing, "Tiptoe Through the Tulips."

You know what?  We cannot escape the history of this instrument, and Tiny Tim had an impact on it.  That should be acknowledged.  It should also be noted that his signature song, "Tiptoe Through the Tulips," existed long before he used it--written in 1929.

Now, about this rendition...I have modified Tiny Tim's recording down a major 3rd so it matches common chord progressions.  He plays it in E, but may be using a ukulele that is tuned A D F# B, which would essentially make the song like playing in D on a GCEA ukulele.

Usually, changing the pitch of a song more than a second makes the audio unrecognizable--in this case, as Tiny Tim uses his falsetto, it isn't as noticeable.  If you want to play along with Tiny Tim's recording at pitch, use a Capo at the 4th fret and use these chords, or tune your ukulele to ADF#B and play it in D (C becomes D, etc.).

Video prepared on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion; ukulele fonts are from Chordette for Education.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/tiny-tim-tip-toe-thru-the-tulips-with-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The More We Get Together Ukulele Play Along (in F) - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-f/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Key of F: F & C7.  The second verse was written by Jim Beloff (author of many ukulele songbooks, including The Daily Ukulele).  The original is in C...I chose to sing this recording in F, as the version in C is too low for my tenor voice.

Accompaniment Created on iReal Pro; Audio copied to Twisted Wave, then exported to GarageBand using AudioCopy.  Ukulele and voice recorded separately via a Blue Snowball microphone into GarageBand--and then all the usual editing with Keynote, Audacity, and iMovie.

The ukulele font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-f/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The More We Get Together Ukulele Play Along (in C) - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-c/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Key of C: C & G7.  The second verse was written by Jim Beloff (author of many ukulele songbooks, including The Daily Ukulele).  This version is really too low for my voice as a tenor, and thus I did record a version in F, which should be just as easy for beginners to play.

Accompaniment Created on iReal Pro; Audio copied to Twisted Wave, then exported to GarageBand using AudioCopy.  Ukulele and voice recorded separately via a Blue Snowball microphone into GarageBand--and then all the usual editing with Keynote, Audacity, and iMovie.

The ukulele font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-more-we-get-together-ukulele-play-along-in-c/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to You Ukulele Play Along - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/happy-birthday-to-you-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  In the Key of G: G, Hawaiian D7, C.

Audio from this original video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qCJSNMqub8g

The ukulele chord font is from Chordette for Education, found at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/happy-birthday-to-you-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I Love the Mountains (Boom de Yada) Ukulele Play Along in C - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/i-love-the-mountains-boom-de-yada-ukulele-play-along-in-c/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  In the Key of C: C, F, Dm, G7.  Transposed down a whole step from the original version by Houaida Goulli.  I have also created a version in the original Key of D.

The original YouTube video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9LEq5sQg2IE

The ukulele font is from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/i-love-the-mountains-boom-de-yada-ukulele-play-along-in-c/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I Love the Mountains (Boom de Yada) Ukulele Play Along in D - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/i-love-the-mountains-boom-de-yada-ukulele-play-along-in-d/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  In the Key of D: D, G, Em, A7.  In the same key as the original version by Houaida Goulli.  I have also created a version that is a whole step lower in the Key of C.

The original YouTube video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9LEq5sQg2IE

The ukulele font is from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/i-love-the-mountains-boom-de-yada-ukulele-play-along-in-d/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Twinkle Twinkle Little Star Ukulele Play Along in C - Key of C, F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/twinkle-twinkle-little-star-ukulele-play-along-in-c/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Twinkle, Twinkle Little Star as recorded by Jewel and pitch dropped to the Key of C (C, F, G7).  However, Jewel temporarily modulates to another key (with the pitch dropped, to the Key of F with F, Bb, and C7).  This is a great song for beginners (maybe skip the Bb?) and the song is also a wonderful example of how a pop/rock star can also sing simple songs (and make them sound good).  I also have uploaded a version in Jewel's original Key of D (which modulates temporarily to the Key of G).

The ukulele font comes from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/twinkle-twinkle-little-star-ukulele-play-along-in-c/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>