<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » Dsus2</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Dsus2</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 19:06:52 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Goodbye Song Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-goodbye-song-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Keys of A and C.  Raised four half steps (400 cents) from the original.

As performed by Bear in the Big Blue House.  Requested by Noreen Jo.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-goodbye-song-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Third Eye Blind - Jumper]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/third-eye-blind-jumper/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/third-eye-blind-jumper/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash - Ain't No Grave]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/johnny-cash-ain-t-no-grave/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Performed by Johnny Cash
Written by Claude Ely

This video is created for an educational purpose. All rights belong to their respectful owners.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/johnny-cash-ain-t-no-grave/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mara's Song Ukulele Play Along]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mara-s-song-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of A.

As performed by Mandy Harvey on America's Got Talent (2017)

This is a great song to learn F#m, and Mandy chose a Dsus2 instead of a standard D chord.  It is a nice departure from songs in C, F, and G (an overwhelming number of ukulele songs are written or transposed to these keys).

If you are playing this during AGT 2017, keep voting for Mandy--and she has a new book out about her life.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/mara-s-song-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>