<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Burl Ives</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Burl Ives</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 15:55:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Burl Ives - Rudolph The Red Nosed Reindeer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/burl-ives-rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along - Christmas

Rudolph The Red Nosed Reindeer - Burl Ives
Written by Johnny Marks

Using the chords: Am  C  C7  D7  Dm  E7  Em  F  G  G7

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/burl-ives-rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Burl Ives - Aunt Rhody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/burl-ives-aunt-rhody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F and F minor.

As performed by Burl Ives.

Have you ever stopped to wonder why so many of our childhood songs are so dark?  Remember...”Ring Around The Rosy” is supposedly about the Black Plague.

I have been looking for more songs to do, and I want to make sure that we are providing content for beginner players, too.  The directory has a lot of one, two, three, and four chord songs.  But I know there are songs that are missing, so I looked in the table of contents for a ukulele method book, and this song is one of the early songs in that book.

Getting past the depressing lyrics (If Aunt Rhody only cared about the goose for a feather bed, she can still do that, can’t she?), the song is strong from a musical perspective—with two chords in a verse, and switching to minor.  You do need to be able to play f minor—but this song would be an effective way to learn.  It is also a little haunting to hear Burl Ives sing in a minor key—creepy.  Apparently “Resident Evil” used this song as well...so if you use this songs with students, prepare to creep them out.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/burl-ives-aunt-rhody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>