<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » Cm7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Cm7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 01:35:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Withers - Lovely Day]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Lovely Day on the ukulele by Bill Withers. The chords used are F Dm7 Bbmaj7 Bbm7 Cm7 Eb C#maj7(Dbmaj7)

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Cooke - A Change Is Gonna Come]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-cooke-a-change-is-gonna-come/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play A Change Is Gonna Come on the ukulele by Sam Cooke. The chords used are Bb Cm7 Gm7 Eb C7 D7 F7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-cooke-a-change-is-gonna-come/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ingrid Michaelson - The Way I Am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Ingrid Michaelson.

I watched Autumn Best’s performance of this song this morning (https://youtu.be/ckcZiDhPYSc) and decided to listen to the original recording—this is a wonderful song with some surprising chords along the way.  Kris Gilbert also has a play along of this video, so check out her version, too (https://youtu.be/FDdVhPdIR_E)

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>