<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Chord » Cm7</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Cm7</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:03:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Withers - Lovely Day]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Lovely Day on the ukulele by Bill Withers. The chords used are F Dm7 Bbmaj7 Bbm7 Cm7 Eb C#maj7(Dbmaj7)

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bill-withers-lovely-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Cooke - A Change Is Gonna Come]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-cooke-a-change-is-gonna-come/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play A Change Is Gonna Come on the ukulele by Sam Cooke. The chords used are Bb Cm7 Gm7 Eb C7 D7 F7.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/sam-cooke-a-change-is-gonna-come/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ingrid Michaelson - The Way I Am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by Ingrid Michaelson.

I watched Autumn Best’s performance of this song this morning (https://youtu.be/ckcZiDhPYSc) and decided to listen to the original recording—this is a wonderful song with some surprising chords along the way.  Kris Gilbert also has a play along of this video, so check out her version, too (https://youtu.be/FDdVhPdIR_E)

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ingrid-michaelson-the-way-i-am/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Perfect Pitch Ukulele Play Along (Updated)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/perfect-pitch-ukulele-play-along-updated/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.   Chords optimized for CGEA ukulele.   Key of F (C7, F, Am, Dm, Bb, C, Cm7, G7, Bbm7, C#7).  The Bacon Brothers dropped this video on Social Media while on tour.  As of yet, there are no chord arrangements of it yet...but as I celebrate my 30th ukulele play along video this month (30 videos in 30 days...or 22 days), I thought I would do something special.  It is a great song, and there is a wonderful reference to "Ukulele Lady" in the instrumental break.  I included their actual video in the play along...hopefully it isn't too distracting from the chords.  A link to that video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B5vWSIe2GCE

Updated for some spelling errors from the original video; remade on Luma Fusion for iOS.

The material, of course, remains the property of the Bacon Brothers...hopefully they are okay with the play along idea.  In the video, some other versions of some of the chords are used (such as C being played with a barre chord), but I tried to use standard root position chords as much as possible.

The ukulele font is from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/perfect-pitch-ukulele-play-along-updated/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Lady Ukulele Play Along (Muppets Version)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ukulele-lady-ukulele-play-along-muppets-version/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Key of F: Key of F: F, C7, Bdim7, Dm, Am, G7, Bb, Cm7.

From the Muppets.  Originally in E (not a great key for ukulele).  Transposed to make it playable!  Original video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uFOvN5FEhsw

There are also famous recordings by Bette Midler.

This one was a bit tricky to figure out...all the versions of Ukulele Lady seem to do their own thing...be ready for the Bdim7 and Cm7 chords.

Ukulele fonts from Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/ukulele-lady-ukulele-play-along-muppets-version/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>