<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » John Mayer</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » John Mayer</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 23:16:10 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mayer - Waiting On The World To Change - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-waiting-on-the-world-to-change/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Waiting On The World To Change on the ukulele by John Mayer. The chords used are C F G Am.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-waiting-on-the-world-to-change/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mayer - Changing - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-changing/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Key of C: C, F, G, Am.  as performed by John Mayer.

Inspired by this cover by Jordan Kiener: https://youtu.be/3Gqz5nXDsPs

This video is unique as it was created 100% on my iPad Pro, using the LumaFusion editing app (and Pixelmator to make some transparent PNGs, Dropbox, and AnyFont--as well as Chordette for Education for ukulele chord fonts--available at ukefarm.com).

One note...during the longer instrumental break, I have the chords switching from F to G.  You could make the case that it should be Dm to G, which is a difference of one note on the ukulele.  However, the whole break is an extension of the previously sung lyrics over F and G...and in the interest of keeping 4 chords (no G7!), I went with F to G.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-changing/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mayer - Waiting On The World To Change - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-waiting-on-the-world-to-change-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[I was able to create this video thanks to my awesome teacher, Dr. Reese. Check out her channel for many more videos like this! https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC5orTW3U5RW_s1gPqkXMfeQ]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-waiting-on-the-world-to-change-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mayer - Waiting On The World To Change - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-waiting-on-the-world-to-change-3/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Uke play along with chord guide
Chords in this tune:  C  Am  F   G
Includes a demo of two strumming patterns

This is John Mayer's "Waiting on the World" transposed to the key of C and edited (instrumental interlude shortened).

I do not own the copyright to this music.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/john-mayer-waiting-on-the-world-to-change-3/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>