<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Cody Simpson</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Cody Simpson</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:20:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cody Simpson - La Da Dee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/cody-simpson-la-da-dee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F.  Original Key.

As performed by Cody Simpson.  Used in "Cloudy With a Chance of Meatballs 2."

I want to thank my student, Ben C., for suggesting this song as a play along.

Beats 2 & 4 are strong in the chorus of this song; you can use the suggested strumming pattern or make your own.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/cody-simpson-la-da-dee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>