<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Genre » Country</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 15:35:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Ray Cyrus - Achy Breaky Heart - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/billy-ray-cyrus-achy-breaky-heart-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Achy Breaky Heart by Billy Ray Cyrus.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.  For educational use.  Chords Used: F & C (or F & C7)

SAME SONG IN C (using C and G or G7): https://youtu.be/Mvx_NsalPkY

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/billy-ray-cyrus-achy-breaky-heart-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Ray Cyrus - Achy Breaky Heart - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/billy-ray-cyrus-achy-breaky-heart/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Achy Breaky Heart by Billy Ray Cyrus.  It’s been raised by 3 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.  For educational use.  Chords Used: C & G (or C & G7)

SAME SONG IN F (using F and C or C7): https://youtu.be/KsjrpecVEoU

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/billy-ray-cyrus-achy-breaky-heart/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lil Nas X - Old Town Road - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lil-nas-x-old-town-road/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fredonia Middle School Ukulele]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/lil-nas-x-old-town-road/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blanco Brown - The Git Up - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/blanco-brown-the-git-up/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Git Up by Blanco Brown.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones to the key of C so beginner instruments can play along.  For educational use.  Chords Used: C (c,e,g) & F (f,a,c).  If playing chords by note, the “D” and “B” notes are never used.

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/blanco-brown-the-git-up/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[9 to 5 - Ukulele Play Along - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/9-to-5-ukulele-play-along/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Working 9 to 5 by Dolly Parton.  It’s been digitally raised by 1 semitone so beginner ukulele students can play along.  For educational use.  Chords Used: G C D A

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/9-to-5-ukulele-play-along/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim McGraw - Live Like You Were Dying - Key of G, A]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/tim-mcgraw-live-like-you-were-dying/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: The first two verses are in the key of G and uses G, C, Em, D, and 1 B7.  The third verse is in the key of A and uses A, D, Gbm, E, and 1 C#.

Live Like You Were Dying by Tim McGraw.  It’s the official lyric video, I just added the ukulele chords.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/tim-mcgraw-live-like-you-were-dying/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[LeAnn Rimes - How Do I Live - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/leann-rimes-how-do-i-live/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: C, G, F, Em7, Asus, A, F-sharp-m, Bm7, Gsus, Dm

“How Do I Live?” by LeAnn Rimes.  It’s been lowered by 2 semitones so inexperienced ukulele players can play along.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/leann-rimes-how-do-i-live/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[What If I Never Get Over You (ukulele play-along) Key C - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/what-if-i-never-get-over-you-ukulele-play-along-key-c/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play What If I Don’t Get Over You on the ukulele by Lady Antebellum. The chords used are C F G Am.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/what-if-i-never-get-over-you-ukulele-play-along-key-c/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams - Jambalaya - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

Chords Used: C, G7

As performed by Hank Williams.

Dr. Reese has had a video of this available for a long time, but the original recording was in a different tuning.  This version has been adjusted to A440.

This video was also blocked on YouTube since it was published (Feb 2, 2019), but the copyright holders recently removed the restrictions on the video.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/hank-williams-jambalaya/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blake Shelton - Wallflowers & Weeds - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/blake-shelton-wallflowers-weeds/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Wallflowers and Weeds on the ukulele by Blake Shelton. The chords used are G C F.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/blake-shelton-wallflowers-weeds/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>