<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » One Direction</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » One Direction</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:52:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Direction - Steal My Girl - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/one-direction-steal-my-girl/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Steal My Girl on the ukulele by One Direction. The chords used are C F G.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/one-direction-steal-my-girl/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Direction - What Makes You Beautiful - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/one-direction-what-makes-you-beautiful/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F.

As performed by One Direction.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/one-direction-what-makes-you-beautiful/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Direction - Story of My Life - Key of D]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/one-direction-story-of-my-life/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chords Used:
A,  Bm7,  D,  Em,  G

I lowered the original tune by a half-step (semi-tone) for playability.
Original lyric video by "directioness" can be found here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kJcFoNIc4Fw

I do not own the copyright to this music. Video is for educational use.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/one-direction-story-of-my-life/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>