<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Chord » Dsus4</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Chord » Dsus4</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 01:35:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Matthews Band - Sweet]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dave-matthews-band-sweet/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of D. (Transposed down one half step from the original recording).

Chords Used: G, D, Bm, A, Em, Dsus4, Bm7

As performed by the Dave Matthews Band.

I'd like to dedicate this play along to my friend and former colleague, Rick, who is a massive DMB fan and has attended more than twenty-five DMB concerts!

Tutorial Video (GCEA & DGBE): https://youtu.be/EDYW9HrCb5U

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is available at ukefarm.com.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6

We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!

Interested in UkeStuff merchandise?  https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And you are invited to visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/dave-matthews-band-sweet/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andie Case - Complicated]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/andie-case-complicated/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Lowered slightly from the Nightcore original.

Chords Used: G, Em, C, D, Dsus4, Em7, Am7

Original Performance by Avril Lavigne; Nightcore version by Andy Case.

Do you enjoy these videos?  If so, please click on the tutorial video and subscribe to the sister channel to this channel.  This channel will feature all video play alongs, and the sister channel will feature all of my original content.

Tutorial Video (GCEA chords & Strumming/Finger Picking): https://youtu.be/-z6dC9kb7Og

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is from ukefarm.com.

The Motion background video is from newlifechurch.tv/resources/motion-backgrounds

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/andie-case-complicated/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Workout Masters - Just Give Me a Reason]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/workout-masters-just-give-me-a-reason/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G. (Original Key)

As performed by Pink, ft. Nate Ruess.

This song was a request from a comment on the Ukulele Tenor YouTube channel.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/workout-masters-just-give-me-a-reason/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Romantics - What I Like About You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-romantics-what-i-like-about-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Note: as of 3/26/2019, this video is blocked in 140 countries, but not in the United States.

For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

As performed by the Romantics.

Moving background from downloops.com.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Ukulele, available at ukefarm.com.

There is a master list of all similar play along videos at my blog: ukestuff.info.  Access to the blog, and all materials on the blog is free.

Want to make a song suggestion?  Follow the link and fill out the form!  https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScvgacvP7hB46DGeJ8o6Gsn7V8JAPsHFo7G-Q4TkiHsILBiAw/viewform?usp=sf_link

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.   Patreon rewards include access to my “method” of the video play alongs (to be used in a classroom) as well as some other resources, and starting in 2019, a chord sheet of every song posted as a play along.

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/the-romantics-what-i-like-about-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Queen - Crazy Little Thing Called Love ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/queen-crazy-little-thing-called-love/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Crazy Little Thing Called Love - Queen
Written by Freddie Mercury

Using the chords: A  Bb  C  D  Dsus4  E7  F  G

Suggested Strum Patterns: DU DU U DU

there are places in the song where you'll need to use DU DU DU DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/queen-crazy-little-thing-called-love/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Varios Artistas - Jar of Hearts]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/varios-artistas-jar-of-hearts/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.  Two steps higher than the original (pushing the edge of audio transposition)!

As performed by Christina Perri.

There is a version in F which requires barre chords.  This version does not.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/varios-artistas-jar-of-hearts/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oasis - Wonderwall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/oasis-wonderwall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Em, G, C, D, Dsus4, A7, A7sus4.  Syncopated strum pattern. See the Wonderwall Strum Guide Video (https://youtu.be/4dqoZWCVoVM).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/oasis-wonderwall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phillip Phillips - Gone, Gone, Gone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/phillip-phillips-gone,-gone,-gone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulule Play-Along
I raised the pitch of the song up a half-step.
The chord names sound very complicated but they aren't. Check out the beginning of the video to see how they are so closely related. It's really interesting!
Strumming and picking suggestions provided.

I do not own the copyright to this music. Video is for educational and instructional purposes]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/phillip-phillips-gone,-gone,-gone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>