<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Glee Cast</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Glee Cast</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 22:12:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glee Cast - Somebody That I Used To Know]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/glee-cast-somebody-that-i-used-to-know/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Somebody That I Used To Know - Gotye (feat. Kimbra)

Using the chords: Bb  C  Dm

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU D DU or D XU D XU (X=chuck)


This video is meant for educational purposes and ukulele lessons.

No copyright infringement intended.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/glee-cast-somebody-that-i-used-to-know/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glee Cast - Feliz Navidad]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/glee-cast-feliz-navidad/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.

Chords Used: C F G (or G7) Am

Glee’s cover version of Feliz Navidad by sung by Artie Abrams (Kevin McHale) In Season 4 Episode 10.  It’s been lowered by 2 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.


If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.


Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video? First, check the index of play alongs at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available. If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6 .  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/glee-cast-feliz-navidad/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glee Cast - Wake Me Up Before You Go-Go]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/glee-cast-wake-me-up-before-you-go-go/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

The original song is by Wham, in C.  This version was originally in Bb (transposed up a whole step) as perfomed by the cast of Glee.

I had made a version of the original Wham! recording, but it was blocked in many countries.  This version seems to be used for lyric videos, so hopefully it will be accessible.  It is a very good cover of the original.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/glee-cast-wake-me-up-before-you-go-go/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>