<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Avril Lavigne</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Avril Lavigne</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:20:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Avril Lavigne - Complicated]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avril-lavigne-complicated/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G.

Chords Used: G, Em, C, D, Am

As performed by Avril Lavigne.

This video was originally blocked everywhere by the copyright holder.  The copyright holder has now allowed this use of the song, so I can make this video available.  Recorded in May 2019, published in July 2019.

Tutorial Video (GCEA Chords & Strumming): https://youtu.be/7sP-4H11k0g

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is available at ukefarm.com.   The motion background is from motionbolt.com.

Interested in UkeStuff merchandise?  https://teespring.com/stores/ukestuff

Check out the UkeStuff Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.   Available on Radio Public, Apple Podcasts, Google Play, Spotify, and Stitcher.

And please visit my ukulele blog/website, ukestuff.info (free).

Thanks for watching the videos and supporting the channel!  Your support of these videos and subscription to the channel makes it possible to produce this content.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avril-lavigne-complicated/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Avril Lavigne - Head Above Water]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avril-lavigne-head-above-water/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Head Above Water on the ukulele by Avril Lavigne. The chords used are F Bb C Dm. (video also available in G)

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/avril-lavigne-head-above-water/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>