<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:03:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley - Santa Claus Is Back In Town]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/elvis-presley-santa-claus-is-back-in-town/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[▶ Check out my gear on Kit: https://kit.com/AndyRamos

This tutorial will show you how to play Santa Claus Is Back In Town on the ukulele by Elvis Presley. The chords used are C F C7 F7 G7.

For those teaching elementary -  F7 can be just played as an F.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/elvis-presley-santa-claus-is-back-in-town/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley - Blue Christmas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/elvis-presley-blue-christmas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F.  Transposed up a half step from the original Key of E.

As performed by Elvis Presley

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

The colored font matches Aquila KIDS ukulele strings.

This version matches the educational Color Chord approach and uses four chords: C (red sticker), G (green stickers), F (yellow stickers) and Am (blue sticker).

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/elvis-presley-blue-christmas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>