<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Bruno Mars</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Bruno Mars</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:36:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - The Lazy Song]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-the-lazy-song/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Lazy Song by Bruno Mars.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.  The lyric video was created by YouTuber gizmothing1, I digitally lowered the recording so you can play it without a capo and added the ukulele chord diagrams.  The original lyric video may be found here - https://youtu.be/k1_26Iayp1s .  For educational use.  Chords Used: G C D B7 Am Bm Em

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-the-lazy-song/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Marry You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Marry You - Bruno Mars

Using the chords: Bb  F  Gm

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU or D DU D DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Count on Me]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-count-on-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Only C, Em, Am, G, F...add Dm on the pre-chorus.

Check out the website for the ukulele jam sessions I run via Fredonia Ukulele: https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.e...

Check out my website for music teachers:
https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.e...]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/bruno-mars-count-on-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>