<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Bruno Mars</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Bruno Mars</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 23:36:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - The Lazy Song - Key of G]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-the-lazy-song/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Lazy Song by Bruno Mars.  It’s been lowered by 4 semitones so beginner ukulele students can play along.  The lyric video was created by YouTuber gizmothing1, I digitally lowered the recording so you can play it without a capo and added the ukulele chord diagrams.  The original lyric video may be found here - https://youtu.be/k1_26Iayp1s .  For educational use.  Chords Used: G C D B7 Am Bm Em

If you found this video useful please subscribe.  If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Do you have a request for a song to be made into a video?  First, check the index of play along videos at www.ukeplayalongs.com to make sure your song isn't already available.  If it isn't, please fill out this request form: https://forms.gle/84rgm7kFNJWnTqFB6.  We cannot promise that a request will be made into a play along, but we do appreciate your recommendations!]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-the-lazy-song/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Marry You - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Marry You - Bruno Mars

Using the chords: Bb  F  Gm

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU or D DU D DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Count on Me - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Count On Me on the ukulele by Bruno Mars. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Em.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Count on Me - Baritone Ukulele - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me-baritone-ukulele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Count On Me on the ukulele by Bruno Mars. The chords used are C F G Am Dm Em.

If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on the bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion. The uke chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me-baritone-ukulele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Count on Me - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Bruno Mars.

Time for a good question: Why make this play along when others have done so?  Simple answer...I had to make a practice track for my choirs and the end result was a file so close to the original that it took less than 10 minutes to edit and render the video to YouTube.  In addition, this video utilizes all of the techniques that I have been learning over the last year of making videos.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Just the Way You Are - Key of F]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-just-the-way-you-are/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of F.  Three chords, although one is Bb.  With the repetition and slow changes, this is a great song to work on that Bb.  One educational warning...the lyrics at one point talk about a "sexy" smile...hope your students can handle that!

As performed by Bruno Mars.

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-just-the-way-you-are/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Count on Me - Key of C]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me-3/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Only C, Em, Am, G, F...add Dm on the pre-chorus.

Check out the website for the ukulele jam sessions I run via Fredonia Ukulele: https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.e...

Check out my website for music teachers:
https://sites.google.com/a/fredonia.e...]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me-3/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>