<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Artist » Bruno Mars</title>
    <link>http://ukealong.com</link>
    <description>Artist » Bruno Mars</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 02:15:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Marry You]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ukulele play along

Marry You - Bruno Mars

Using the chords: Bb  F  Gm

Suggested Strum Patterns: D DU U DU or D DU D DU


This video is meant for educational purposes.

No copyright infringement intended]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-marry-you/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruno Mars - Count on Me (EP Version)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of C.

As performed by Bruno Mars.

Time for a good question: Why make this play along when others have done so?  Simple answer...I had to make a practice track for my choirs and the end result was a file so close to the original that it took less than 10 minutes to edit and render the video to YouTube.  In addition, this video utilizes all of the techniques that I have been learning over the last year of making videos.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Check out the Ukulele Video Play Along Podcast, where I talk about ukulele education and my own ukulele experiences.  Available on Apple Podcasts and Google Play.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[http://ukealong.com/song/bruno-mars-count-on-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>