<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Demi Lovato</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Demi Lovato</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 21:57:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Demi Lovato - Sober]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/demi-lovato-sober/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[This tutorial will show you how to play Sober on the ukulele by Demi Lovato. The chords used are C F G Am.

*Note - this video contains mature subject matter, no foul language. It's not a video I usually do but with so many people struggling with addictions, mental health issues and just struggling with life, I found the raw emotions and openness compelling.


If you found this video useful please subscribe and share with your friends. If you want to be notified of future videos please click on bell next to subscribe.

Video created on the iPad using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/demi-lovato-sober/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Demi Lovato - Let It Go]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/demi-lovato-let-it-go/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of G (Original Key)

As performed by Demi Lovato.

I also created a play along of “Let It Go” from the movie Frozen, but there are a few more twists and turns harmonically in that version (https://youtu.be/FyyWuj-jS1U).

There is one part of a verse in this version where a Dm and Cm are substituted for D and C...that’s kind of fun...watch for it.

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.

Are these ukulele resources valuable to you?  If so, consider following my blog at ukestuff.info, and becoming a patron at www.patreon.com/cjrphd.  There is a master list of all similar play along videos at ukestuff.info.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/demi-lovato-let-it-go/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>