<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Uke Along Artist » Tiny Tim</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Artist » Tiny Tim</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 19:59:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tiny Tim - Tip Toe Thru' the Tulips with Me]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/tiny-tim-tip-toe-thru-the-tulips-with-me/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  Optimized for GCEA Ukulele.  Key of C.

In my opinion, two things led to the decline of the ukulele in the late 1960s (continuing until the early 2000s).  The first was the emergence of guitar-based rock (and people wanting to be rock stars), and the image of Tiny Tim.  As part of his "gimmick," Tiny Tim played the ukulele and sang in a weird falsetto, causing an entire generation to associate the ukulele with being a weirdo and maybe even a freak.  When you look deeper at Tiny Tim, he was an accomplished musician but he also knew how to make his mark using a gimmick.

See: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wMbQsKJ64S0

A number of factors led to the re-emergence of the ukulele in the early 2000s, but even today some people have the mental image of Tiny Tim when they think of the ukulele.  I even had a teacher come up to me at a convention and start singing, "Tiptoe Through the Tulips."

You know what?  We cannot escape the history of this instrument, and Tiny Tim had an impact on it.  That should be acknowledged.  It should also be noted that his signature song, "Tiptoe Through the Tulips," existed long before he used it--written in 1929.

Now, about this rendition...I have modified Tiny Tim's recording down a major 3rd so it matches common chord progressions.  He plays it in E, but may be using a ukulele that is tuned A D F# B, which would essentially make the song like playing in D on a GCEA ukulele.

Usually, changing the pitch of a song more than a second makes the audio unrecognizable--in this case, as Tiny Tim uses his falsetto, it isn't as noticeable.  If you want to play along with Tiny Tim's recording at pitch, use a Capo at the 4th fret and use these chords, or tune your ukulele to ADF#B and play it in D (C becomes D, etc.).

Video prepared on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion; ukulele fonts are from Chordette for Education.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/tiny-tim-tip-toe-thru-the-tulips-with-me/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>