<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Jazz</title>
    <link>https://ukealong.com/</link>
    <description>Genre » Jazz</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:49:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Bublé - Sway ]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-bublé-sway/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For educational use.  Optimized for GCEA ukulele.  Key of Dm.

As performed by Michael Bublé.

The original shifts up a half step at the end...this version stays in Dm.  This is a great song to play/sing!

Need to practice at a different tempo?  Use the gear icon in the video (lower right) to slow down (or speed up) the tempo at pitch!  Need to do so on an iPad or iPhone?  Check out the browser called "iCab Mobile" which has a Module called "Video Playback Rate"

Video created on the iPad Pro using Luma Fusion.  The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education, available at ukefarm.com.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/michael-bublé-sway/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[La La Land Cast - Another Day Of Sun]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/la-la-land-cast-another-day-of-sun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  In the Key of G and G#.  There are fifteen chords in all.  These are listed on the second screen of the video.

The original song is in Ab and A...and it becomes much easier to play in F.  However, the original audio becomes strange if the pitch is modified that much.  Therefore, I dropped the audio a half step to G...resulting in this play along.

The last section modulates a half step...this is pretty easy to do with the barre chords provided.  That said...you need to be ready for them.

This is not a ukulele play along for beginners...but it is a great song, and advanced players should have some play along videos that challenge them, too!

The original video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lV5XmoWC8Mo

The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education available from ukefarm.com.  I did have to manually create some of the second position barre chords for the video (the text and chords were prepared in Keynote)]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/la-la-land-cast-another-day-of-sun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Larry Clinton - Heart and Soul]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/larry-clinton-heart-and-soul/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For Educational Use.  As performed by Larry Clinton and His Orchestra.  In the Key of C ( C, Am, F, G7, Dm, C7, E7, A7, B7), with some surprises in the less familiar portion of the song.

There are some very quick chord changes and chord ambiguity in those same less familiar verses.  These didn't work out as well as I would have hoped for...but the main instructional point is repetition of C, Am, F, G7, following the instructional materials used by the Tampa Bay Ukulele Society.

The original video comes from: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pNjpTOB4ksY

My apologies to every music teacher who cringes as students play this song on the piano!

The ukulele chord font is Chordette for Education from ukefarm.com]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://ukealong.com//song/larry-clinton-heart-and-soul/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
</channel></rss>